Lyokowinter基于人人影视等爱好者翻译修正制作
靠近点
Come in close.
再近点
Closer.
因为你认为你看到的越多
Because the more you think you see,
你就越容易被骗
the easier it'll be to fool you.
因为什么叫看到？
Because what is seeing?
你是在看 但是你是在过滤、解释它
You're looking, but what you're really doing is filtering, interpreting,
寻找个中意义
searching for meaning.
我的工作？
My job?
是接受你给我最珍贵的礼物 你的注意力
To take that most precious of gifts you give me, your attention,
使用它来欺骗你
and use it against you.
芝加哥
周一
Chicago
Monday
我在现在要开始翻牌了
I'm going to flip through this deck.
我想让你看一张牌
And I want you to see one card.
不是这个 这个太明显了
Not this one. That's too obvious.
仔细注意了
Pay close attention.
那太快了 我再做一遍
That was too fast. I'll do it again.
你准备好了么？
Are you ready?
好的
Okay.
- 现在你看到了一个么？ - 是的
- Now did you see one? - Yes.
- 你心里记住了一个么？ - 是的
- Do you have one in mind? - Yes.
现在 你看到你的卡片在这么
Now, do you see your card here?
没
No.
那是因为你离得太近了去看
That's because you're looking too closely.
一整晚上我都跟你们说了什么了
And what have I been telling you all night?
你越近去看
The closer you look...
你看的东西越少
The less you see.
新奥尔良
NEW ORLEANS,TUESDAY
现在看我的眼睛
Now look into my eyes.
睡觉 好了
And sleep. Okay.
然后
And...
如果你能从我这拿到这张钞票 那就归你了
If you can get this bill from me, you can have it.
继续 拿吧 拿去
Go ahead. Take it. Get it.
如果你能说出你得名字 那也可以
If you can say your name, you can have it.
好的 待在这 等一下
All right, just hang out there, wriggle a sec.
我要偷瞥一眼
I'm gonna take a little peek under the hood
- 你丈夫脑袋里面在想什么 - 哦 不 不 不
-of your hubby's brain. - Oh, no, no, no.
我在构想
I'm picturing...
- 不要告诉我 - 当然
- Don't tell me. - Of course.
海滩 鸡尾酒
Beach. Cocktails.
佛罗里达？
Florida?
听着 是一次出差旅行
Look, it was a business trip.
某种意义上的公事
I mean, it is a kind of business.
也许是陈年旧事
Maybe the oldest business.
你知道么 爱的亲 让我们
You know what, Honey Bee, let's...
她不能移动，Mack
She can't move, Mack.
你在想一个女人的名字
You're thinking of a woman's name.
A B C
A! B! C!
D E F G
D! E! F! G!
H I J
H, I, J...
J？Jean Jane Janet
J? Jean. Jane. Janet.
谁是Janet?
Who's Janet?
你认识Janet？
You know Janet?
不是你最好的朋友 对么？
It's not your best friend, is it?
当然不是
Of course not.
- 你的妹妹？ - 不是 别酱紫
- Your sister? - No, please.
她的妹妹 哦 我的天
Her sister? Oh, my God.
你不光是出差
You weren't away on business.
- 你是因Janet出差 - 不
- You were away on Janet. - No.
你老婆的妹妹
Your wife's sister!
好的 我们需要挪到这里
Okay, we need to move over here,
因为看起来她现在有点恼火
because it seems like she's a little bit upset right now.
你想让一切这都过去吗?
You want this to go away?
- 是的 - 好的 把你钱包拿出来
- Yes. - Okay, pull out your wallet.
快啊 拿出来
Come on, get it out.
你对每个人都这样勒索么？
Do you shake down everybody like this?
不 只针对少数殊特人士。
No, only the special few.
这是多少 200刀怎么样
What is this? Two hundred seem fair?
你懂个啥啊？ 这事关重大，来250刀吧
You know what? This is a big deal. Let's go $250.
你是一个打劫的艺术家
You're a stick-up artist.
是啊 当然
Yeah. Of course.
好了 睡吧！
Okay, and sleep!
现在 当我打响指
Now, when I snap my fingers,
你会忘了这一切
you won't remember any of this.
还有你 Warren Beatty
And you, Warren Beatty,
每次你看到甚至想到Janet
every time you see or even think of Janet,
脑中都会构想我裸体的样子
you're gonna picture me naked.
那可没什么好看
And that's not a pretty sight.
是啊
Yeah.
还有...你醒了！
And... You're wide awake!
我们尽力了
Well, we did the best we could,
但是有些人没法被催眠
but some people just aren't to be hypnotized.
- 我做错了什么 - 来吧 亲爱的
- I did it wrong? - Come on, Honey Bee.
不 你做得很好 - 我请你吃晚饭
- Oh, no, you did it fine. - Let me buy you dinner.
照顾好她
Look after her.
先去ATM机取点钱
Just have to hit an ATM first.
约纽
星期三
女士们先生们，我是下一个伟大的魔术师
Ladies and gentlemen, I am the next great magician,
谁能告诉我这个魔术是怎么变的
and I will give $100
我就给谁100美元
to anyone who can tell me how this trick is done.
我从Brooklyn的Mel's Deli熟食店拿到的一个普通的勺子
I have an ordinary spoon from Mel's Deli, right here in Brooklyn.
检查一下
Check it out.
现在 所有人都全神注意
Now, everyone please pay very, very close attention.
因为我要用意念把这个勺子掰弯
Because I'm about to bend this spoon with my mind.
谢谢谢谢四周传一下
Thank you. Thank you. Pass that around.
- 这是什么 - 你在干什么.老兄
- What's this? - What are you doing, man?
看看这个！ 看起来我们拿到了一个勺子和一个柄
Look at this! Looks like we got a spoon and a stem.
我会还其他魔术
I've got other tricks.
或者你可以给我100刀
Or you could give me my 100 bucks.
你说的你会给钱
You said you would.
钱包不错
Nice wallet.
先生 你的眼神不错
You have a very good eye, sir.
谢谢
Thanks.
我的钱包
Wallet.
我的钱包，我的手表！
My wallet. My watch!
拦住那个家伙！
Stop that guy!
拦住那个穿皮夹克的家伙！
Stop that guy in the leather jacket!
他拿了我的钱包！
He's got my wallet!
洛杉矶，星期四
Los Angeles,Tuesday.
好了 洛杉矶
Okay, Los Angeles,
准备好欣赏压制大戏了么？
are we ready to end this thing?
没错
Yeah!
当时器计归0时
When that timer hits zero,
装满的食人鱼的箱子
a tank full of flesh-eating piranhas
将会从这落下
will fall from above.
女士必须被铐住.对么 姑娘们
A lady has to have handcuffs. Right, girls?
1 2 3
One, two, three!
好的
Yeah!
救命！ 快停下！
Help! Stop it!
她是认真的！ 她逃不出来！
She's serious! She can't get out!
快找人去帮助她
Go get some help!
快帮忙 伙计
Help, dude!
快闪开！ 闪开！ 闪开！
Get out of the way! Move! Move!
得了吧！ 真是扯淡！
Come on! This is bullshit!
设计这个魔术的人是个变态的虐待狂！
Whoever thought of this is a sick sadist!
没错！
Yes!
我是你的铁粉
I am your biggest fan.
看得出来， 你在“攻击”我的脸
I could tell by the way you're attacking my face right now.
关上门 烂公寓
Close the door. Bad apartment building.
- 魔术师 到这来 - 好
- Magician, come here. - Okay.
- 等下 等下 -什么？ 什么？
- Wait, wait. - What? What?
你怎么做到的
How did you do that...
大楼上的方片七？
The seven of diamonds on the side of the tower?
- 是的 - 那是商业机密
- Yes. - That's a trade secret.
我可以给你点提示 我贿赂大楼的电工
I'll give you a hint. It involved bribing the tower electrician.
多少钱
How much?
50刀
50 bucks.
- 但是太难了 - 哦 谢谢
- But it's so hard. - Oh, thank you.
只能是方片七么？
Is it always a seven?
我可以有52种不同的方式变那个魔术
I could do that trick 52 different ways.
你能玩52种花样在我身上么
Can you do 52 different tricks on me?
我尽力
I'll see what I can do.
魔术师！
Magic man!
我喜欢你的洗发水味
I love your shampoo.
- 起来 - 什么？
- Hold up. - What?
你该走了
You need to leave.
你在逗我么
Are you kidding me?
哦 我的天 这太令人难堪了
Oh, my God, this is so embarrassing.
这就是你这种人吗？
Is this what you do?
你对女人玩的变态花样？
Some kind of sick trick you do to women?
东埃文街45号
"45 East Evan Street."
别担心我会打给你的
Don't worry about it. I'll call you.
你没有我的号码
You don't have my number.
我是魔术师我会找到的 晚安
I'm magic. I'll find it. Have a good night.
你就是个混蛋
You are such an asshole.
嘿！
Hey!
Henley
Henley.
Danny？ 嘿
Danny? Hey.
你收到一个卡片 嗯？
You got a card, huh?
不 不 不 对你是好的 恭喜你
No,no,no, it's good for you. Congratulations.
好吧 这就是我要做的
All right, so here's what I'm gonna do,
我要进去我要查看这个地方
I'm gonna go inside. I'm gonna scope the place out.
你等在外面我会回来接你的 好么
You wait out here. I will come back
别进去
and get you, okay? Do not come in.
嘿 丹尼！ 我再也不是你的助手了
Hey, Danny! I'm not your assistant anymore.
头发挺好看
Nice hair.
那么 事实上 你在忙什么呢
So, actually, what have you been up to?
我觉得你很清楚我在忙什么 Danny
I think you know exactly what I've been up to, Danny.
在我的网站上 我能看到你所有的匿名动态
I saw all your anonymous posting on my website.
你有一个网站  不错啊
You have a website. That's good.
你才不错 能说出这个词
Good for you. Get the word out.
好吧
Okay.
所以显然我们中没有人是唯一的选择
So apparently none of us was the only one chosen.
让我成为第一个打开话闸的人吧
Let me be the first one to kick my ego to the curb.
让一下
Yeah. Excuse me.
- 门是锁着的 - 是么？ 我看看
- Door's locked. - Is it? I'll check.
你  等等 不要告诉我
You. Now, hold it, don't tell me.
Helen 不 不
Helen? No, no.
Henley
Henley.
在你的咖啡杯上写着呢
It's on your coffee cup.
谢谢你拆我台
Thanks for keeping me honest.
顺便提下 那不是读心术
That wasn't mentalism, by the way.
只是一种观察
It was just an observation.
再一次观察 你很漂亮
Second observation, you are beautiful.
谢谢
Thank you.
很好不错非常悦耳 很好
That's good. That's very nice. Very well-polished. Nice bit.
J．Dannel Atlas.很高兴见到你
J. Daniel Atlas. Nice to meet you.
很好 我知道你是谁
Very nice. I know who you are and I just want to say that
我只想说我对你对我们施展
I'm not interested in you doing
的读心术不感兴趣
your mentalism thing on us.
特别是我们不知谁把我们带到这或甚至不知这是否是真的
Especially when we don't know who brought us here or even if it's real.
等下 我感觉...我感觉你是一个控制狂
Hold on, I'm sensing... I'm sensing you are a control freak.
对不起 我们以前见过么？
I'm sorry, have we met before?
不用读心术也看得出来
It doesn't take a mentalist to figure that out.
你是一个控制狂
You are a control freak.
好吧 我把它当做一种称赞
Well, I take that as a compliment.
只有他会把它当做一种称赞
Only he would take it as a compliment.
好吧 很好 不错 另一个称赞
Okay, great. Good. Another compliment.
好了 所以那就是为什么你们不再在一起了
Okay. So that's why you're no longer a couple.
我们是一对？ 不 不
A couple? No, no.
我们从没有在一起
We were never a couple.
他去过常常把我锯开两半
He used to saw me in half.
她是一个很好的助手
She was a very good assistant.
但是对于Danny来说我太胖了
But I was too fat for Danny.
不 那次我那么说是因为那暗门
No. I said that one time because of the trap door.
- 有固定规格的 - 你把它造成制这么小
- There were specs. - You built it this size.
没有人能穿过去 没有人
No one could fit through there. No one.
Rebecca就可以
Rebecca fit through.
Rebecca一直都可以
Rebecca fit for years.
你知道穿着那些小衣服
Do you know how hard it is to stay
有多难受么
in those tiny little costumes?
不 我是主角
No. I'm the main attraction.
好吧那么他永远不会让你感到出众
Okay. So he never made you feel special.
相信我 你应该对自己的才华抱多点信心
And, trust me, you deserve to be made to feel special.
那真是一个好故事
That's a really nice story.
希望你们搭档愉快
Hope you guys enjoy each other's company.
不会吧
No way.
J．Dannel Atlas?
J. Daniel Atlas?
老兄 我看过你以前所有的表演
Dude, I've seen everything that you have ever done.
你就像
You're like...
我崇拜你真的
I idolize you. Seriously.
你的真实粉丝  见到你太好了
From a true fan. It's so nice to meet you.
顺便说 我是杰克
I'm Jack, by the way.
问题来了 你收到这其中之一了么？
Question. Did you get one of these?
以下均为塔罗牌角色
是的死神
Yeah. Death.
大祭司
The High Priestess.
我的是爱神
I'm the Lover.
3分钟
Three minutes.
隐士
Hermit.
那么 我们是..我们是等某个人？
So, what are we... Are we waiting for someone?
- 我们为什么要... - 门锁着的
- Why are we just... - The door's locked.
哦 不会 没有东西永远锁着
Oh, no, nothing's ever locked.
这是什么地方？
What is this place?
哇哦 我还以为我的公寓是算脏的了
Wow. Thought my apartment was nasty.
这里冷死了
Man, it's freezing in here.
那是什么？
What's that?
不知道
I don't know.
上面写着什么？
What's it say?
现在你不（出自《Now You See Him,Now You Don't》）
"Now you don't."
玫瑰不因其名而香
"A rose by any other name..."
伙计们 发生了什么？
Guys, what's happening?
看看那个
Look at that.
是气体！
It's gas!
放松只是干冰
Relax. Just dry ice.
酷
Cool.
等下你觉得这一切都是什么
Wait. What do you think this is all about?
等等 等等
Hang on. Hang on.
我啥也没想到
I got nothin'.
好的 谢谢 谢谢 你耽误了时间
Okay. Thank you. Thank you for the delay.
我只是想给大家几秒的思考时间
I'm just trying to create the space for wisdom.
好吧 所以你就像佛陀
Okay, so you're like Buddha,
假设他不是那么聪明
if he wasn't so enlightened.
你就像耶稣
And you're like Jesus,
假设他有那么傲慢和他所有的奇迹都是假的
if he was arrogant and all of his miracles were fake.
好了 公共场合不要打情骂俏
Okay, lovebirds, get a room.
Danny 老实说 你是做的么？
Danny, be honest. Did you do this?
不等下是你么
No. Wait, did you?
我希望是
I Wish.
为什么你们没人问我是不是我做的
Why didn't anyone ask me if I did it?
哦 很好
Oh, great.
没电
Electricity is out.
好的 让我检查一下
Well, let's check.
蓝图
Blueprints.
太难以置信了
They're incredible.
你认为是谁做的这个？
Who do you think did this?
我不知道 但是我真的想见到他们
I don't know, but I really want to meet them.
是一个表演
It's a show.
惊天魔盗团 I
一年之后，拉斯维加斯
Las Vegas,One year later.
Merritt McKinney
Merritt McKinney,
Daniel Atlas
Daniel Atlas,
Henley Reeves
Henley Reeves,
Jack Wilder
Jack Wilder.
Arthur Tressler携手 MGM大酒店荣誉呈现
Arthur Tressler and the MGM Grand proudly presents
天启四骑士
The Four Horsemen.
谢谢
Thank you.
今晚我们要尝试一些
Tonight we would like to try something
好吧 让我做一些与众不同的尝试
that will, well, set us a bit apart.
我们的闭幕演出
For our final trick,
我们要做一些
we're gonna do something never before
拉斯维加斯的舞台上从未有过的
seen on a Las Vegas stage.
或者任何的舞台上从未有过的
Or any stage for that matter.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
今晚
tonight
我们要去抢劫一个银行
we are going to rob a bank.
这是让人很兴奋的犯罪
That's a lot of excitement for a crime.
我已经开始激动了你们呢 观众们
I'm getting excited. What about you, people?
1 2 3
One, two, three!
对不起 先生这里完全不允许拍摄
Sorry, sir. There's absolutely no recording allowed
在表演期间
during the performance.
哦 是么 好 当然
Oh, yeah, yeah, sure, of course.
让我把它收起来
Let me just put this away.
实际上 我需要拿走
Actually, I need to take that.
在表演之后 我会把它还给你
After the show, I can come and give it back to you.
好吧
Okay.
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay.
现在 请 请安静
Now, please, please, settle down.
现在谁在这有一家银行想让我们去抢
Now who here has a bank they would like us to rob?
这里很多人对银行都有仇啊
That's a lot of people with a vendetta.
那么我们随机选一个
So we'll choose one at random then.
我的助手将会确保挑选是随机的.对吧
My associates will make sure it's random. Right?
Elvis 帮帮我 - 非常感谢
- Elvis, help me out, bud. - Thank you very much.
在Jack的容器里面有写着区域号的乒乓球
In Jack's bowl are ping pong balls with section numbers.
Jack 能扔我一个区的数字吗
Jack, could you hand me a section number?
谢谢 是B区
Thank you. We are looking at Section B.
B区在哪
Where is Section B?
好了 可能是你们其中一个 准备
Okay. There. It's gonna be one of you guys. Get ready.
我不明白为神马你们也这么高兴
I don't know why everybody's happy.
中奖的只是她们
It's only them.
Merritt 我能拿一个座排号吗
Merritt, can I get a row, please?
谢谢你  Merritt
Thank you, Merritt.
我们要找第5排的
We are looking at row number 5.
在哪
Where is that?
还有亨利 随机找个座位号
And Henley, could I please have a random seat number?
噢 幸运之号13
Oh. Lucky number 13.
B - 5 - 13的观众 你在哪
B-5-13. Where are you?
先生请站起来 你在这 你好
Sir, please, stand up. There you are. Hi.
你能确认一下
Could you just confirm for me that this
你的座位号么 B - 5 - 13
is, in fact, your seat? B-5-13.
是的
Yes.
好的很好现在 你能告诉我们
Okay. Wonderful. Now, could you please tell us
你的名字和你银行的名字么？
your name and the name of your bank?
我的名字是Etienne Forcier
Well, my name is Etienne Forcier.
我的银行是巴黎共和信用社
And my bank, it's Credit Republicain de Paris.
法国人 好的
French. Okay.
我们希望能有更本地的银行
We were hoping for something a little more local,
一些没有什么安保的信用社
a kind of mom-and-pop credit union with no security.
但是没事一言既出驰马难追
But that's fine. A promise is a promise.
你能登上舞台么
Could you please come up to the stage
我们要抢你的银行
and we'll rob your bank.
他趁上台我说一句
And while he does that...
今晚上这的某个人
There is someone here tonight
没有他们
without whom we would just be
我们只是四个巡回演出的魔术师
four magicians working the circuit,
想要得到
trying to get...
实际上 想要到这
Well, actually, trying to get here.
你或许认识这个人
You probably know this man,
如果不是这么多人中的一个
if not from one of the many, many
他旗下有许多家公司
companies he puts his name on.
他是我们的朋友他是我们的捐助者
He is our friend. He is our benefactor.
Mr. Arthur Tressler
Mr. Arthur Tressler.
请 站起来  Art 请站起来
Please, stand up, Art. Please, stand up.
他是这里唯一一个
The only man here with
有女王的电话号码的人
the Queen's cell phone number.
实际上 请站好 Art
Actually, please, stay standing, Art.
我想说当我们找到Mr. Tressler时
I want to say that when we came to Mr. Tressler,
我们保证过 作为一个团队，我们会成为
we promised that, as a unit, we could become
魔术界的翘楚
the biggest name in magic.
所以我们想说 “谢谢你”
So we wanted to say, "Thank you."
顺便说下 Art  你可以看到
And by the way, Art, you notice on the sign out front,
我们确保把你的名字写在上面
we made sure we put your name on top.
如果你能做到
If you turn out to be as good
像你想的一样好 亲爱的姑娘
as you think you are, dear girl,
那我的名字就不是太必要了
that won't be necessary much longer.
我们还没有完成压轴大戏
We haven't done our closer yet.
为什么你不先看看
Why don't you watch it
然后自己做决定呢
and then you can decide for yourself.
女士们先生们  Arthur Tressler
Ladies and gentlemen, Arthur Tressler!
谢谢当然 再一次感谢
Thank you. And, of course, once again,
目光回到Merritt McKinney
the Cardinal of Clairvoyance, Merritt McKinney.
Etienne  Jack现在带到了舞台上的东西
Etienne, what Jack is bringing to the stage now,
在我们魔术世界中被称为瞬间传送头盔
is what we in the magic world call a teleportation helmet.
你需要戴上这个 它可以让你
You will need to wear this, as it will allow you
自由地穿梭时间和空间
to literally fold through space and time
到你的银行所在
to your bank in the...
第8区
8th?
- 第9区 - 是的
-9th arrondissement. - Yeah.
现在 一旦你在那
Now, once you are there,
我们能够通过这个头盔和你说话
we will be able to speak with you through this helmet.
现在如果
NOW if...
哦 天啊 太漂亮了
Oh, my God, that's beautiful.
它很时尚很有吸引力
It has the added attraction of being very stylish.
是时候让法国人向美国人学学时尚了
It's about time the French learned from America on that subject.
它是一件很漂亮的头饰么？
Is that a beautiful piece of headgear?
- 谢谢 谢谢 - 是的
- Thank you. Thank you... -it is.
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you very much.
但是在你出发之前
But before you go anywhere,
请你 挑一张卡 任何一张都可以
could you please, pick a card, any card.
不是那个
Not that card.
不 这是老式美国玩笑  你可以挑那张
No, that's an old American joke. You can take that one.
好了 这张？
Okay. This one?
给你的朋友们展示一下 不要给我们看
Show it to your friends in Section B. But not to us.
好了 很好 现在你只需要把你的名字签在这
Okay, great. Now if you could just sign your name there.
- 是的 - 如果可以话用英语
- Yes. - In English, if possible.
- 很好 - 谢谢
- That's good. - Thanks.
放到你的口袋里
Put it in your pocket.
现在还差一个小细节
And now for one tiny detail.
现在 Etienne 请走进到这精妙的装置里
Now, Etienne, let's step into this cockamamie contraption.
我得退出来  祝好运
And I'll step off of it. Bonne chance.
维加斯这里是晚上11点50
It's 11:50 p.m. here in Vegas.
巴黎是早上8点50
That's 8:50 a.m. in Paris.
你的银行10分钟内开门
Your bank opens in less than 10 minutes.
One,
two...
Three.
怎么回事？
What the fuck?
Efienne？
- Efienne? - Efienne?
计划中不是这样的吧，是吧
It wasn't supposed to happen like that, was it?
Efienne？
Efienne?
我喜欢那个法国佬
I liked that little French guy.
他去哪了？
Where did he go?
同一时间，巴黎
Pari,at the same moment.
等下 他在这
Wait, there he is.
不 不 不 不 拜托 安静下
No, no, no, no, please, please, please.
我是 Daniel Atlas  你能听到我么
This is Daniel Atlas. Can you hear me?
Etienne？你还好么
Etienne? Are you okay?
是的
Yes.
很好 你在那看到什么？
Perfect. What do you see in there?
钱
Money.
这是真的么
Is this real?
是的  看起来有300万欧元
Yes. Looks like three million or so Euros' worth.
好了 现在 我需要你做的是
Okay, now, here's what we're gonna need you to do.
我想你从你的口袋里拿出
I want you to take the card that you signed
你签过名的那张牌
out of your pocket.
我想让你拿出
And I want you to take the ticket stub
今晚演出的门票的存根
from tonight's show
我想让你把她们
and I want you to put it right there
放到钱中间
in the middle of the money.
现在 扔掉它
Now drop it.
现在 在你头盔的一边你可以摸到一个按钮
Now, on the side of your helmet you should feel a button.
现在还别按
Don't press it just yet.
那个按钮能激活一个空间通道
That button activates an air duct
连接巴黎和拉斯维加斯
that connects Paris to Las Vegas.
好了 很好 现在你可以按了
Okay, good. Now you can press it.
好了 现在 Etienne 抓紧了
All right, now, Etienne, hold on tight.
你或许会感到要被吸走
You might feel a bit of a vacuum.
等一下
Wait a second.
该死
Ah merde!(法语)
谢谢你 Etienne．谢谢 各位
Thank you, Etienne. Thank you, everyone!
我们是天启四骑士
We are The Four Horsemen.
晚安！
And good night!
Good night!
等下
Hold up here.
Dylan Rhodes
Dylan Rhodes.
什么 我听错了吧
What? I don't think I heard you correctly.
你是说的魔术师？
Did you say magicians?
是的 迪伦 魔术师
Yeah, Dylan, magicians.
你现在在哪
Where are you now?
我在Aria．我现在要上去抓他们
I'm at Aria. I'm heading up there to grab 'em now.
联邦调查局 把手举到我能看到的地方
FBI! Hands where I can see them.
上 抓住他们 快点
Let's go. Get 'em up. Come on.
上 抓住他们
Let's go. Get 'em up.
把书放下
Put the book down.
好了你抓到我了
Okay. You got me.
- 不许动 举起手来！ - 哦 我勒个去
- Freeze! Hands in the air! - Oh, my!
谁介意帮们我拿一下我们的行李箱
Do one of you guys mind giving us a hand with our bags?
跟我走
Let's go.
老大 请告诉我这是一个玩笑
Boss, please tell me this is a joke.
我刚刚收到Willy Mears指认Paulie Attanasio
I just got Willy Mears to finger Paulie Attanasio.
我一个月，顶多两个月
I'm a month, two tops,
才弄明白这个案子
away from blowing this whole thing open.
让Turkelson干这玩意
Get Turkelson.
他在亚特兰大
He's in Atlantic City.
Cowan呢？ 找他
What about Cowan? Look at him.
他就坐在那
He's just sitting there on his ass.
真好笑 Rhodes
Hilarious, Rhodes.
我爱你
I love you.
混蛋
Asshole.
我没有时间管这魔术这破事
I don't have time for this magic crap.
这破事刚刚从巴黎的银行偷了300万欧元
This crap just pulled three million Euro out of a Parisian bank.
- 他们偷了那么多？ - 是的
- That's how much they got? - Yeah.
实际上 320万欧元
Actually, 3.2.
她是谁
Who is she?
你是谁
Who are you?
国际刑警组织的Alma Dray
Alma Dray from Interpol.
我会和你一起调查
I'll be working the investigation with you.
你一定在逗我
You gotta be kidding me.
让我去抓
It's bad enough they got me chasing down
David Copperfield（著名魔术师）和他的朋友们已经够糟糕了
David Copperfield and Friends.
现在还要强迫我承担多个--无意冒犯--国际刑警？
Now I'm being saddled with, no offense, with Interpol?
我也很期待和你一起共事 Rhodes探员
I look forward to working with you, too, Agent Rhodes.
对不起 我认为不需要你的帮助 好么
I'm sorry. I don't think I'm gonna need your help on this. Okay?
- 那个法国佬在哪？ - 我已经跟他谈过了
- Where's the French guy? - I already spoke to him.
哦 是么 你在我之前跟我的证人谈过了
Oh, you did? You spoke to my witness before me?
你的证人 我还以为你不想接这案子
Your witness? I thought you didn't want the case.
再说 他没什么价值
Besides, he's useless.
哦 真的么 为什么？
Oh, really? Why is that?
因为他相信他们的魔术是真的
Because he believes their magic was real.
哦 他相信魔术是真的？
Oh, he believes the magic was real?
你是对的 他或许没用
You're right, he probably is useless.
国际刑警也不介意我们跟他谈谈吧
Is it okay with Interpol if we talk to him, too?
谢谢
Thank you.
我一生中从没偷过东西 好么
I have never stolen a thing in my life, okay?
我试图把这钱还回去 但是他们不收
I tried to give the money back, but they won't take it.
好吧 好吧 好吧让我们说说你抢的银行
Okay, okay, okay, let's just say you robbed a bank.
- 我干的 - 好吧很好你做的
- I did. - Fine. Fantastic. You did.
但是我是刚接手的 你能给我解释一下
But since I'm new to this, can you explain to me how you went
你是怎么在三秒钟内从拉斯维加斯到了巴黎呢
from Las Vegas to Paris in three seconds?
使用瞬间传送头盔
With the teleportation helmet.
好吧 这究竟是怎么回事？
Okay, what the hell is going on here?
他在表演期间被催眠了
He was hypnotized during the show.
我跟你说过 他没使用价值
I told you, he's useless.
等我处理完其他混蛋
Okay, I'll deal with you when I'm clone
再找你算账
with this other bullshit.
嘿！
Hey!
在演出中 一半的观众被催眠了
During the show, half the audience was hypnotized
以为他们是在交响乐团
to believe they were in the Philharmonic.
我猜那个 “混蛋” 是触发字
I guess that "bullshit" was the trigger word.
好了 嘿 嘿.Ecoutez . Etienne 从那下来
Okay. Hey, hey. Ecoutez. Etienne, come on down from there.
你不在交响乐团
You're not in the Philharmonic.
- 怎么用法语说停下来？ - 停下来
- How do you say "stop" in French? - Stop.
告诉他停下来
Tell him to stop.
不，我不能 你只能让他演奏完
No, I can't. You just have to let him finish his movement.
好吧 我需要暂停休息
Okay, I need a time-out.
那屋里法国人太多了
Too many French people in one room.
Agent Rhodes
Agent Rhodes!
我受命而来 要调查出个结果
I'm ordered by my bosses to provide a report.
我就在这 不管喜欢还是不喜欢
And until we have one, I'm here, like it or not.
要么合作
So we can work together,
要么就跟在我后面
or you can continue to follow behind
再问一遍我问过的问题
asking the same exact questions I'm asking.
你来决定
It's up to you.
我还没说完呢
I'm not finished.
我刚刚飞完12个小时 漫长的一天
I just flew 12 hours, after what was already a long day.
我还没处理好时差呢
And I do not handle jet lag well.
如果你想知道谁的脾气更大
So if you want to see who can be grumpier,
我保证你肯定会输
I promise you, you will lose.
好吧 这几个白痴中
Fine. So which one of these idiots
你想先审哪个呢？
do you want to talk to first?
他？
Him?
Dylan 郑重声明
Dylan, for the record,
读心术从没被证实过
mentalism has never actually been proven to be accurate.
好吧
Okay.
那就是说 那不是科学
That is to say, that it's not a science.
更多是娱乐
It's more for entertainment.
好吧
All right.
这个家伙说的什么也别相信就这样
Just don't believe everything the guy says. That's all.
请允许我表达我真诚的歉意
Please convey my deepest apologies
对你外面的同事
to your colleague out there.
我很抱歉整个变装星期二的事情
I'm really sorry about this whole Tranny Tuesday thing.
我太过火了
I was out of line.
变装星期二?
Tranny Tuesday?
是他和他妻子的约定
Well, it's an arrangement he and his wife have.
或者没有 如果你相信
Or might not have, if you believe
所有Fuller探员说的都是对的
everything Agent Fuller is saying to be correct.
不过嘛 在FBI里面有大男人
But isn't there a proud tradition in the FBI
穿裙子的光荣传统吗
of men wearing dresses?
不丢人 富勒探员 不丢人
No shame, Agent Fuller. No shame.
我说着玩的
I'm just having fun.
这是你的牌么？ 不
Was this your card? No.
瞧 我就知道你不是选红心皇后那种女士
See, I knew you weren't a queen of hearts lady,
我欣赏这一点
and I respect that.
当我没绑在这里 我能玩的更好
The trick usually works better when I'm not strapped in here,
但是我懂规定
but I understand protocol.
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay.
所以 如果你与此事无关
So, if you had nothing to do with it,
那张魔术卡牌是怎么进入金库的
then how did the playing card get into the vault?
哦 是啊.那便是所谓的
Oh, yes. That would be...
现在的孩子怎么称呼它来着?
What do the kids call it these days?
哦 想起来了 魔术
Oh, yes, that's right. Magic.
回答问题   “天才”
Just answer the question, okay, smartass.
好吧对不起 对不起 对不起
All right. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
这送你 不要分享给他
You can keep that. Don't share it with him.
这上面写你是个读心者
It says here you are a mentalist.
准确来说读心术是什么？
What exactly is mentalism?
大部分是戏法 用一些科学
Tricks, mostly. Some science.
针对性的猜测或许是最贴切的描述
Targeted guessing might be a most apt description.
通过直觉和偶尔
Along with some intuition and the occasional...
我脑中闪过的灵光
Voices in my head.
据说你在这方面相当知名
Says here you were fairly famous at one point.
你甚至可以通过电话催眠
You can even hypnotize people over the phone.
有几年还在全美进行大型巡回演出
Some big tours around the U.S. for a few years,
- 出过两个电视专题节目 - 光辉岁月
-two TV specials. - Glory days.
然后你哥兼经纪带着你所有挣得钱消失了
Then your brother/manager disappeared with all your hard-earned money.
你做的功课很足吧
Did your research, did you?
国税局审计  欠税
IRS audit. Back taxes.
你重返舞台的过程一定很不容易吧 对吧
You've had a long hard slog back into the limelight,haven't you.
McKinney先生
Mr. McKinney?
是的 的确是 我很多谢你揭我伤疤
Yes, indeed, it has. And I do appreciate that trip down Memory Lane.
据我所知 当来自巴黎的那个人
As far as I understand it, when the man from Paris
带上那顶魔术头盔
put on the magical helmet...
听我说
Listen to me.
就算你没有抢银行 你也是知情者
If you didn't rob that bank, then you knew about it.
所以你是共犯
Which makes you an accomplice.
所以如果你今天想离开这那么 我建议你开始
So if you wanna walk out of here today, I'd suggest you start...
现在给我听好了  除非你觉得
Now you listen to me, unless you think
在内华达州有一个检察官
there's a D.A. in the state of Nevada
会愿意把这个案子提交给陪审团
who'd be willing to make sense of this to a jury,
最后还得放我们回去演出
then we have a show to perform.
还有你  Rhodes探员
And you, Agent Rhodes,
得回去重新理理思路了
have a drawing board to get back to.
这是你们第一次约会？
Is this your first date?
什么
What?
不 我是说 很明显 你们俩家伙之间互相不了解
No, I mean, obviously, you guys don't know each other well, if at all.
但是 就像这屋里却有一种微妙的紧张感
But, like, there is a palpable tension in this room.
在你参与进来之前
And before you get involved,
你应该考虑这个事实她有很多大秘密
you should consider the fact that she has a lot of big secrets.
而且我知道的第一个是
And I know the first one is that
这是你第一次外勤任务  对么
this is your first time off the desk. Isn't it?
你本应该对他说点什么
You should have said something to him.
对于你来说是个奇怪的方式
This is a weird way for you to find out.
你简直是在央求被捕.你知道么
You are literally begging to be arrested. You know that?
前提是你真会这样做  但是你不会
If it means you would actually do it, then, yeah. But you won't.
因为你这么做了 那意味着你
Because if you did, it means that you,
还有FBI还有你的国际刑警的朋友
and the FBI, and your friends at Interpol,
实际上会在某种程度上相信魔术
actually believe, at an institutional level, in magic.
一定会让媒体哗然的
The press would have a field day.
而且我们就比我们现在出名多了
And we'd be even more famous than we already are.
而你们这些家伙看起来
And you guys would look like idiots
比现在更像白痴
even more then you already are.
不 不是你  是他 好吧？
Well, no, not you. But him. Right?
用我们行话来说就是 你们说
You have, what we in the business, like to call,
袖子什么也没有
"nothing up your sleeve."
你明白的
And you know it.
别让他迷上你然后又甩了他
Don't draw him in and then dump him
因为抛弃对于他来说是一个很大的 “心理阴影”
because abandonment is a big "area" for him.
妈妈
Mommy?
爸爸
Daddy.
你跟爸爸有很大问题
You have big daddy issues.
- 好吧 够了 - 我来告诉你
- Okay, that's enough. - I'll tell you what.
你的心理治疗师平均每次收你200 - 300美元
Your average therapist is gonna charge you $200-$300 for this sesh.
我 我只要10块
Me? I'll take a tenner.
如果你觉得不差这点钱
Okay, later, if you're feeling magnanimous,
我还是只要10元
I'll still take a tenner.
想知道你那张椅子之前都有谁坐过吗？
You wanna know who sat in that chair before you?
黑帮头目 谋杀犯 和小偷
Mob bosses, murderers, and thieves.
你知道谁把他们抓到这的么？
And you know who put them there?
现在坐在你面前的人
The guy who's sitting in this chair.
所以我警告你 我能保持我的决心的时间远比
So I warn you, I can maintain my resolve much longer
你能保持你那种傲慢态度长
than you can maintain that phony arrogance.
一旦你引以为豪的表情露出
And the instant that you even show
哪怕一丁点破绽
the slightest crack in that smug facade,
我都会穷追不舍
I'll be there.
我会一直都在
I will be all over you like...
就像依附在你身上？
Like white on rice?
对不起 那不公平
Sorry. That's unfair.
让我警告你
Let me warn you.
我要你听着
I want you to follow.
因为无论你认为你知道什么
Because no matter what you think you might know,
我们都会永远领先你一步
we will always be one step, three steps,
三步 七步
seven steps ahead of you.
并且当你认为你追上来时
And just when you think you're catching up,
那时我们已经在你身后了
that's when we'll be right behind you.
不管什么时候
And at no time will you be anywhere other than
你只会被我牵着鼻子走
exactly where I want you to be.
所以尽管靠近点 放马过来
So come close. Get all over me
因为你觉得自己越接近
because the closer you think you are,
你看到的越少
the less you'll actually see.
我要抓住你
I'm gonna nail you...
那瓶苏打是不是有什么问题，小姐？
Something wrong with that soda, Miss?
哦！ 次奥！
Oh! Shit!
魔术的第一守则
First rule of magic.
永远做房子里最聪明的人
Always be the smartest guy in the room.
老大 我们在做什么？ 我们就这样让他们走了？
Boss, what are we doing? We're letting them go?
他们都承认他们会再做一次
They all but admitted they're gonna do it again.
半小时前你对他们毫不在意
About a half an hour ago, you didn't give a damn about them.
- 怎么变了？ - 我见识过他们了
- What changed? - I met them.
嘿 伙计们
Hey. Guys.
嘿 我查了一下观众
Hey, I ran a check on the audience.
大部分是拿来充数的
Most of it was just filler.
都是被Tressler拉去的
People that Tressler dragged in to pack the room.
但是猜猜谁坐在后面
But guess who was sitting there in the back,
把全过程都拍了下来？
filming the whole damn thing?
我不知道
I don't know.
Thaddeus Bradley
Thaddeus Bradley.
那个上过电视表演拍过很多DVD和节目的家伙
Thaddeus Bradley, the guy from TV with the DVDs and shows?
不
No.
好吧 他给魔术揭秘
Okay, well, he debunks magicians.
他揭露他们 他给你展示他们是怎么变得魔术
He exposes them. He shows you how to do their tricks.
给他打电话
Get him on the phone.
打过了 约了45分钟后与你共进午餐
I did. You're having lunch with him in 45.
很好
Good.
Bradley先生 - 开始时 - 也是个魔术师
Mr. Bradley started as a magician.
- 他当时真的很棒 - 真的么
- He was actually quite good. - Really?
- 其中之一 - 我猜也是
- One of the best. - You don't say.
看穿表象的天才
"The greatest genius is in seeing through the illusion."
真是个热爱工作的男人
That's a man who loves his work.
你觉得我不能用一杯葡萄酒引起你的兴趣
You sure I can't interest you in a glass of wine?
不 不 不 不 谢谢 先生我们在工作
No, no, no. No, thank you, sir. We're working.
我倒想来一杯
I will take one.
太不可思议了  太棒了
That's incredible. That's amazing.
红色染料 藏在手里
Red dye, palmed.
耶稣就酱玩的么（红酒被认为是耶稣的鲜血）？真不可思议
Is that how Jesus did it? That's incredible.
对不起我能占用一分钟么？
I'm sorry. Can I just take a minute here?
你以前是最伟大的魔术师之一 为什么你不干了呢
You were one of the great magicians. Why did you stop?
你知道有多少人想看现场魔术表演
Do you know how many people went to see magic performed live
在过去的五年中
in the last half decade?
大约有160万
About 1.6 million.
你知道在这一时期我卖了多少DVD么
You know how many DVDs I sold in the same period?
500万
Five million.
好吧 那是因为钱
Right, so it's about the money.
钱只是一部分
Well, the money is only there
想获知真相的人远比乐意被蒙在鼓里的人多
because the need to know is greater than the desire to be fooled.
就像你 我恨那些就会欺骗无知观众的钱的人
Like you, I detest those who prey upon the gullibility of the masses.
恕我直言 这场游戏中没有代价么
With all due respect, isn't there a cost, though, to this game?
代价？
Cost?
我不知道 比如事业
I don't know. Careers.
生命
Lives.
我猜你指的是Lionel Shrike
I assume you're referring to Lionel Shrike.
不好意思 谁
I'm sorry, who?
Lionel Shrike
Lionel Shrike.
30年前淹死在哈德逊河的一个二流魔术师
A middling magician who drowned in the Hudson River 30 years ago.
Bradley先生第一次做专题节目揭示Shrike所有的魔术
On Mr. Bradley's first special, he revealed all of Shrike's tricks.
第二年 Shrike试图东山再起
The next year, Shrike tried to stage a comeback.
他被关在一个保险箱
He was shackled inside a safe,
被丢到河里
and dropped into the river.
但是他再没有浮上来
But he never resurfaced.
你是说他死了？
You mean he died?
我没害死他
I didn't kill him.
他的死是因为他挑战了他不能运用自如的魔术
He killed himself trying to do something he wasn't prepared to handle.
你应该明白这是场游戏了吧
You do realize this is a game?
相信我 这不是一个游戏
Believe me, it's not a game.
那就是一个游戏
It is a game.
你本身就是游戏。被人玩弄于鼓掌之中
You're the game. You're being played.
你对我百般讨好就是为了获得我的信任
And your pathetic attempts at fawning to gain my trust...
得了吧
I mean, come on.
你被看穿了
You got me.
如果你真的想知道
If you really want to know
在拉斯维加斯的舞台是怎么打劫巴黎的银行
how a bank in Paris was robbed from a stage in Las Vegas,
我下个月会出专题节目
my special comes out next month.
或者我可以指控你妨碍公务
Or I could just bring you in
或者强迫你告诉我
on obstruction charges and force you to tell me.
除非 当然 你想告诉我
Unless, of course, what you're trying to say to me is that
其实你也不知道他们怎么做的
you actually don't know how they did it.
表演技巧和舞台效果
Showmanship and theatrics.
当一个魔术师挥舞着他的手然后说
When a magician waves his hand and says,
这是魔术开始的地方
"This is where the magic is happening."
真正的魔术在别的地方开始
The real trick is happening somewhere else.
错误引导 最基本的魔术概念
Misdirection. A basic concept of magic.
对魔术的概念没兴趣
Not interested in the concepts of magic.
我只想知道他们怎么抢银行的
I wanna know how they robbed a bank.
如果你认为他们抢了银行那你就是一个笨蛋
You're an idiot if you think they robbed a bank.
但是不用信我的话
But don't take my word for it.
去巴黎旅游一趟如何？
How about a trip to Paris?
Hermia 拿上瞬间传输头盔 请 亲爱的
Hermia, the teleportation helmet, please, darling?
你在开玩笑 对么？
You're joking, right?
你想不想知道他们怎么做的？
You wanna know how they did it or not?
我要把这个戴到你头上
I'm just gonna put this on your head.
过来吧
Step right up.
就这样
There you go.
现在我们把这个拉下来 安全又舒适
Now we just pull this down all safe and snug.
放松 可以了
Make yourself comfortable. There we go.
当你准备好了去巴黎
And when you're ready to go to Paris,
随便说个魔术咒语
just say the magic word.
去我的？
Blow me?
- 这就可以了 - 一路平安
- That'll suffice. - Bon voyage.
你好（法语）
Bonjour.
我个人选择从楼梯去巴黎
I personally prefer to take the stairs to Paris.
欢迎来到光之城 Rhodes探员
Welcome to the City of Light, Agent Rhodes.
呵呵 那你要我戴头盔干嘛
Hardy har har. What was with the helmet?
恶搞
My fun.
什么
What?
没什么
Nothing.
所以他们造了个仓库
So they got a vault set.
是的
Yes.
而且完全复制了
And it's the exact replica
那个小法国佬的银行
of the little French guy's bank.
所以他是个托
So he's a plant.
他是棋子，不是托
He was a dupe, not a plant.
他们选择了他  他们知道他坐在哪
They chose him. They knew which seat he was in.
不 不 不 观众选的座位
No, no, no, the audience picked the seat.
除非 当然  不是观众选择的位置
Unless, of course, the audience didn't pick the seat.
他们让观众觉得他们选了位置
They let them think they picked the seat.
我们会随机选择一位
We'll choose one at random then.
实际上 他们把事先准备好的球
Actually, they were just palming the ball
藏在掌心用来替换
with the seat number they wanted.
我们在找第5排
We are looking at row number 5.
Henley 能告诉我座位号吗？
Henley, could I please have a seat number?
幸运号码13
Lucky number 13.
你能确认一下这个是你的座位号吗
Could you just confirm that this is, in fact, your seat?
他是被选中的
He was selected.
他们给他暗示让他去拉斯维加斯
They programmed his mind to make him go to Las Vegas.
拉斯维加斯万岁
Viva Las Vegas.
然后他们不断强化催眠 直到他做到了
And then they kept reinforcing it, until he did.
他们跟踪他
They trailed him.
研究他
They studied him.
这一切都不是靠运气
Nothing was left to chance.
我有他的资料了
I got his measurements.
他不知道他是他们的目标
He had no idea he was their target.
他们只要想把他在拉斯维加斯激活就好了
And they simply activated him in Vegas.
当我打响指
When I snap my fingers...
再一次 梅里特・麦金尼
And once again, Merritt McKinney.
但是他怎么知道他是哪个银行的
But how did they know what bank was his?
- 你在开玩笑 - 真的么
- You're kidding. - Really?
你能再蠢点么？
Can you be any more of a condescending ass?
是的
Yes.
就像这样
Like this.
魔术师有一个非常罕见的 很神秘的方式
There's a very rare, very mysterious way
去占卜一名观众的银行
in which a magician divines an audience member's bank.
你准备好了么？
You ready?
是的
Yes.
信用卡
Credit card.
那就是他们如何拿到牌上的签名
And that's how they got the signature for the card
然后留在了巴黎的金库里面
they left in the vault in Paris.
很好
Very good.
你被人领先了 Rhodes探员
You're being one-upped, Agent Rhodes.
好了 但是他们还得把签了名的牌放进金库里啊
Okay, but they had to get the signature card in the vault.
你刚才说他们没有偷那些钱
You said they didn't steal the money.
不 我并没有这样说
No, I didn't say they didn't steal the money.
我说他们没有抢劫银行
I said they didn't rob the bank.
我猜测他们的盯上
My guess is that they targeted
运钞车上的一批刚印出来的钱
a shipment of freshly minted money
送往那个法国人的银行的钞票
headed to the Frenchman's bank on-board an armored truck.
当然 也很难进去
Which, of course, is just as hard to break into.
除非你已经在里面了
Unless you're already inside.
尽管银行不会承认
And despite what the banks would have you believe,
开这些卡车的人都不是精神强大的人
the men who drive these trucks are not exactly mental giants.
对于我们的骑士
For our Horsemen,
太容易搞定了
it was almost too easy.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, boys.
那怎么让假钱从金库消失的？ 那是什么？
So, how did they make the fake money disappear from the vault? What is that?
闪光纸（特殊加工纸，燃烧不留灰不引燃其他易燃物）
Flash paper.
魔术师经常使用它们
Magicians use it all the time.
不产生烟 不留灰烬
Creates no smoke, leaves no residue.
两天前 没有人听说过这些家伙
Two days ago, no one heard of these guys,
但是今晚他们表演的门票在35秒内便被抢购一空
but tonight's show sold out in 35 seconds.
我想他们已经向世人解释了表演的真谛
I think these guys have cracked the secret to show business.
那就是给你的观众300万美元
Give your audience $3 million.
让他们有个好心情 对么？
Puts 'em in a good mood, doesn't it?
有史以来最好的结局
Best finale ever.
他们会成为载入史册的第一批魔术师
They're gonna be the first magicians in history to get laid.
记住 如果氧气罩掉下来了（指飞机失事）
Remember, if the oxygen mask comes down,
首先先给律师带上  记着哦 是的
put it on the lawyer first. Remember. - Oh, yes.
我总是这样做   律师优先
I always do. It's lawyer first,
- 然后是我自己然后是孩子 - 然后是你自己
-then myself and then the children. - Then yourself.
是的 然后是孩子
Yes. Then the children.
允许我来说说我们俩一直共同思考的问题吧
Allow me to make plain what we've both been thinking.
那是什么
And what's that?
很明显 你对丹尼尔有感觉
Well, obviously, you have feelings of affection for Daniel.
不求回报且一往情深
Unrequited and misguided,
因为他根本就是情感无能的
owing to his lack of emotional availability.
因此 你便十分的...
Consequently, you're very tightly...
怎么说呢
How should I put it?
憋屈
Corked.
哦 是吗？
Oh, I am？
现在 既然你的生理需求得不到满足
Now, recognizing that you have physical needs not being met,
本着友好互助的精神
and strictly in the vein of helping a sister out,
你可以考虑一下让我做你的私人备胎
I invite you to think of me as your own personal corkscrew.
哇哦 谢谢
Wow. Thanks.
让我仔细考虑那个廉价和没有意义的性建议
Let me mull over that offer of cheap and meaningless sex.
也许廉价或者没有意义 但不是在浪费时间啊
Cheap and meaningless, maybe, but not time-consuming.
我们可能会提前几分钟抵达
We should be getting there a few minutes early.
所以坐回去 放松
So, sit back, relax.
我们即将抵达新奥尔良（别称是Big Easy）
We should be in the Big Easy soon.
再次感谢您乘坐本次航班
Appreciate you flying with us today.
那么 对 Tressler来说除了能得到钱还有什么
So, what's in it for Tressler, besides the money?
自尊心
Ego.
好吧 选一张牌
Okay, pick your card.
看一下 然后放在桌上 然后告诉我
Look at it, put it in the deck, and tell me.
不 别告诉我
No, don't tell me.
- 好的 - 好的
-Okay. -Okay.
Thaddeus那天晚上在那
Thaddeus was there that night.
他完全明白他们是怎么做到的  那他呢？
He knows exactly how they pulled it off. What about him?
你说什么呢？
What are you saying?
你认为他们可能是一伙的
You think they could be working together.
我不知道 我所知道的是这些家伙
I don't know. All I know is that these guys
都是街头魔术师
were a bunch of street magicians
一年前一无所有
a year ago with no resources.
那如果没有外界的某种帮助
So, how do they go from doing that to this
他们是如何从街头魔术师变成现在的名人呢？
without some kind of outside help?
是你的牌么
Is this your card?
不 我的牌在那个家伙身上
No, my card is sitting over there in that guy's lap.
洗牌技术不错
Nice shuffle.
你知道 这挺难的
You know, this is hard.
根据这本书
According to this book,
一些人仅练习其中的一个简单动作就要每天练八小时，年复一年
some of those guys practice one simple move eight hours a day for years.
真的么  这帮人该找点正经事做了
Really? Some of those guys seriously need to get a life.
你是对所有魔术师都有意见么
Is it magicians, in general, you have a problem with?
还是只是对这几个人有意见
Or specifically those guys?
整体来说我对魔术师一点都不感冒
I could care less about magicians in general.
我只是讨厌那些利用别人的人
What I hate is people who exploit other people.
怎么利用他们了？
Exploit them how?
再试一次
Try again.
通过利用他们的弱点
By taking advantage of their weaknesses.
利用其需求使其相信一些无法解释的事物
Their need to believe in something that's unexplainable
来忍受生活中的磨难
in order to make their lives more bearable.
我把它看作一种力量
I see it as a strength.
当我相信它时 我的生活更快乐
My life is happier when I believe that.
这个是你牌么？
Is this your card?
是的
Yeah.
是么
Yeah?
- 是啊 - 酷
- Yeah. - Cool.
你脸上的笑容是真的么？
That smile on your face. Is it real?
或许吧
Maybe.
所以让我问你 探员先生
So let me ask you, Mr. Detective Man.
你觉得被利用了么？
Do you feel exploited?
或者你有一丁点 一丁点快乐
Or did you have maybe a tiny, tiny bit of fun?
个人有去找医生
Guy goes to the doctor.
医生说 先生 你必须
Doctor says, "Sir, you're gonna
要停止手淫
"have to stop masturbating."
他说 为什么
He Says, "Why?"
他说 这样我才能完成对你的体检啊
He says, "So I can finish the examination."
哦 Danny  我能跟你谈谈
Oh, Danny, can I talk to you about
- 我在这个表演中的角色么？ - 可以 可以 好 当然
-my role in the show real quick? - Yeah, yeah, yeah. Sure.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
我们要准备一场表演
We got a show to prepare for.
我们现在开始么
Do we now?
不 不 不 别跟我来这个
No, no, no, don't do that.
不要对我用你那套
You're not doing that thing to me. No.
哪一套 我只是看看你而已
What thing? I'm just looking at you.
才怪嘞  我已经观察你一年了
No, you're not. I've been watching you for a year.
我知道你所有的小把戏
I know all of your little tricks.
你就是这样想的?小把戏？
That what they are to you? Tricks?
没错 都是些小花招 这是 Barnum（美马戏团经纪）说的
Yes, it's gimmicks. it's Barnum statements.
就是看看眼神 读读肢体语言啊 我懂的
It's reading the eyes. Body language. I get it.
如果真是那么简单  为什么你不去对Henley做
If it's such an easy thing, why don't you do Henley?
是啊 Danny 为什么你不对我这么做呢
Yeah, Danny. Why don't you do me?
不 你太简单了我要读Jasmine
No, you're too easy. I'll do Jasmine.
不
No.
读我
Do me.
哦 是啊 是啊 读Art
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Do Art.
好的
Okay.
更容易
Even better.
- 嗯
- Art. - Yeah.
但是我提醒你 我很难被读
But I warn you, I can be difficult to read,
只要我愿意的话
when I want to be.
您就跟着我的节奏来吧
Just stay with me, okay?
那么 Art 你是一个坏孩子
So, Art, you were a tough kid.
是个不折不扣的小流氓
You know, kind of a real rapscallion.
你有一条狗 也是条恶狗
You had a dog. A real tough dog.
十分凶恶  比如一条真正
A brutish breed. Like a real...
我猜是 叫Ben的斗牛犬
I want to say, Ben the bulldog.
实际上 我小时候很虚弱，
Actually, I was a prissy little tot.
我养了一只毛茸茸的白猫叫做Snuffles
I had a fluffy white cat called Snuffles.
对不起
Sorry.
等下 让我试下
Wait, let me try one.
- 我可以做的更好 - 让他来
- I can do way better than that. - Let him do it.
好吧 给我更多的时间更多时间
Come on, give me one more time. One more time.
他可以做的更好
He can do way better than that.
让我们来说家庭
Let's do family.
你在你母亲那边有一个舅舅
You had an uncle on your mother's side.
他有一个很...很阳刚的名字
He had a real, kind of... A real masculine name.
一个听起来很像社会精英的名字
A real, kind of, salt-of-the-earth...
一个十分亲近的
You know, a real stick-it-to-you...
比如Paul或Thompson ? 是Paul?
Like it was some kind of Paul. Thompson? Was it a Paul...
算了  你知道吗？ 我什么也猜不出来
Okay. You know what? I got nothin'.
- 接近了 - 是么？
- Nearly though. - Was I?
是的 我舅舅的名字叫Coshman Armitage
Yeah. My uncle's name was Cushman Armitage.
真的么 Snuffles和Cushman Armitage ?
Really? Snuffles and Cushman Armitage?
那就是你的童年？
That was your childhood?
我非常希望今晚的表演比这好多了
I certainly hope tonight's show is gonna be better than this.
别担心 等着瞧吧
Don't worry. Just you wait.
拜托 告诉我你已经订到房间了
Hey. Come on, give me some good news on a hotel room, please.
什么 你在逗我？
What, are you kidding me?
不 现在是狂欢节，Dylan
No, it's Mardi Gras, Dylan.
根本找不到能够看到剧场的房子
There's nothing within sight of the theater.
等下 等下 那个女的去哪了
Hold on a second. Hold on. Where is this woman?
嘿 嘿！终于找到你了
Hey, hey! There you are.
什么鬼  一个法国女孩刚到新奥尔良
What, the French girl doing a little sightseeing
就观光么
while she's in New Orleans?
不 事实上在这说法语
No. In fact, here, speaking French
是很有用哒
is actually an asset.
你看到那上面的女人了？
Do you see that woman up there?
那是Marie Claire
That's Marie Claire.
她给我们准备了一件很好的公寓
And she has a lovely apartment for us.
不用谢
You're welcome.
好吧
Yeah.
我们找到住的地方了
We got a place.
这里面一边两个  30个人守在周围
I want two each inside of here. The other 30 around here.
屋顶 巷子 阳台
Roofs, alleys, balconies.
-时刻盯着那些魔术师 -是的，长官
- Eyes on The Horsemen at all times. - Yes, sir.
哇 100年前 Wjlliam Robinson 改名为Chung Ling Soo
Wow, 100 years ago, William Robinson took the name Chung Ling Soo
之后一生从未在公共场合说英语
and spent his entire life never speaking English in public.
另一个人 Maximiliian
This other guy, Maximillian...
我现在对魔术的历史不感兴趣
I am not interested in a history lesson on magic at this moment.
如果你想被他们玩在手心 那继续
If you want to keep playing into their hands, go for it.
我在尝试理解他们是怎么思考的
I'm just trying to understand how they think.
你觉得我被他们玩弄于股掌 是么
You think I'm playing in their hands, do you?
我只是不知道那个和这个有什么冲突
I don't know how any of that is gonna go against this.
这个什么？ 魔术？
This what? This magic?
Lionel Shrike
Lionel Shrike.
在中央公园他让观众选了一个牌然后签上名
In Central Park, he has a guy pick a card and sign it.
然后他走向一个有着20年树龄的树
Then he goes to a tree that has been there 20 years.
他们把树锯成两半
They saw the tree in half.
在树里面 封装在玻璃瓶中
Inside the tree, encased in glass,
是那个签名的牌
is the card with the signature.
他怎么做到的
How did he do that?
我不知道 但是我确定有合理解释
I have no idea. But I'm sure there's a logical explanation.
让一下
Excusez-moi
你们有人在那个大厅么？
You guys got a guy in that lobby yet?
不 但是我的确有些好消息
No, but I do have some good news.
记住阿特拉斯是一个控制狂
Remember how Atlas is such a control freak,
他要整个成员都戴上可追踪的手镯
he's got his whole crew on those tracking bracelets?
什么可追踪手镯？
What tracking bracelets?
他让他的每个成员
He has every member of his crew
都戴上一个追踪手镯
wearing a tracking bracelet.
这些手镯是8个频带的
Those bracelets are on a sub-8 flat-band.
所以只要阿特拉斯跟踪他们
So as long as Atlas is tracking them...
下一个
Next.
我们的人就可以在这里移动指挥中心追踪Atlas
...our boys can track Atlas from right here in the mobile command unit.
一有消息就通知我
Okay, call me if you get any movement.
收到
Copy that.
你没看到全局  Dylan
You are missing the big picture here, Dylan.
巴黎的有个地方 Pont des Arts
There is a place in Paris, Pont des Arts.
有些早上我坐在长凳上
Sometimes in the mornings I sit on a bench there.
看着人们许愿
And I watch the people make a wish
然后锁一个锁在桥上
and lock it in a lock on the bridge.
他们把钥匙扔到塞纳河
Then throw the key into the Seine.
- 整天都有人这么做母亲 情侣 老人
All day they do this. Mothers, lovers, old men.
看着钥匙沉到河里
Watching the key sink into the water
他们的秘密被永远地锁住
and their secret is locked away forever.
真实而又神奇
Real and, at the same time, magical.
那么
So,
你真的觉得有可能还会有第5位骑士么？
do you really think it's possible there's a fifth Horseman?
是的
Yeah.
和Thaddeus Bradley一起揭开魔术的神秘面纱
MAGIC UNMASKED WITH THADDEUS BRADLEY
传说中古埃及曾有一个神秘团体
There is a legend of a secret order born in ancient Egypt called
称为“眼睛”
"The Eye."
据说 其成员会苦练手上功夫
It is said they perfected sleight of hand
从法老那里偷食物
to steal food from the Pharaohs
然后分给奴隶
and give it to the slaves.
他们的目的是什么？
Their purpose?
使用魔术和错觉来平衡正义的天平
Using magic and illusion to even the scales of justice.
这几位天启骑士们会否与一众蠢人相信这个神话呢？
Are The Horsemen next in a long line of fools to believe this myth?
他们能逃脱法律和逻辑么 就像他们在拉斯维加斯做的
Will they evade the rules of law and logic like they did in Las Vegas?
还是这片南部沼泽的暗黑秘术
Or will the dark mysticism of this Southern swampland
比他们更好
get the better of them?
很好 Bradley先生
Bravo, Mr. Bradley.
除非你有禁止令
Either you have a cease-and-desist,
我猜你没有 否则你应该离开
which you don't, or you should leave.
如果我想让什么停止
If I want something to cease or desist,
它就停止
it does.
休息一下
Take five.
根据你潜在的赞助商来算
According to your potential backers,
从这部最出色的片子中
you stand to make 2.5 million tops
你最多可以挣250万
from your best special.
我这里有张支票
I have here a check
350万美元
for 3.5 million.
让我走开么
To walk away?
是飞走 我的私人飞机随时可供你调遣
To fly away. My jet is at your disposal.
我们不要再开玩笑了  Tressler先生
Let's not kid ourselves, Mr. Tressler.
你是想把他们捧出名吧
You're in this to ride them up.
而我就是要让他们名声扫地
I'm in it to ride them down.
我觉得我们没什么可谈吧
I take it that we do not have a deal.
这也是我们之间的矛盾
And therein lies our conflict.
我直话直说
Let me be blunt.
我银行账户里的钱你可不能比
My bank account is much, much bigger than yours.
但是我的律师团队也更强大
And my lawyers are much stronger.
他们会用各种各样的禁令
And they will manacle you
让你寸步难行
with so many injunctions.
直到你站在一边，无助的看着
Until you stand by, hopelessly watching
你所拥有的一切
everything that you own drain away
从你贪婪的小眼下飘过
in front of your greedy little eyes.
这不是我第一次收到威胁了
This isn't the first time I've been threatened.
可我还是好好地站在这
And I'm still here.
不过 这可是你第一次被我威胁
It is, however, the first time you've been threatened by me.
如果你敢搞砸我的投资
And if you do anything to sully my investment,
如你所言，让他们声名扫地的话
the ride down, which you mentioned,
会立刻 马上惹出严重的祸事
will be sudden, precipitous, and measurable on the Richter scale.
你不应该这么做的
You shouldn't have done that.
根据迷信说法
According to superstition,
人使用娃娃发泄愤怒
one who uses a doll to enact one's own wrath,
将给自己带来同样的愤怒
is likely to bring that very wrath unto himself.
有趣吗
Isn't that funny?
我还以为你不信魔术的
And I thought you didn't believe in magic.
帮我个忙
Do me a favor.
幻想一个你最刺激很性感的性体验
Visualize your most adventurous sexualexpe?ence.
没门 你个变态
Stay out of my head, you perv.
如果我不读你的思想  怎么能上你
Well, no, if I stay out of your head, I'm never gonna get into your pants.
好吧 我们继续练习吧
- Right. - So let's stick with this exercise.
这有利于...   原谅我的冒犯
- And it helps... - Pardon the intrusion.
我希望晚上一切顺利
I just wanted to wish you good luck tonight.
然后你可以在网上曝光我们吗
What, so you can try to expose us later on your little website?
需求量可大了
And on demand.
那是不可能的 - 是吗
- That's not gonna happen. - Oh, no?
因为天眼而用一架特殊的飞机？
Operating on a special plane because of The Eye?
听说那地方很不错 有月光、星光
I heard it's a lovely place. Lots of starshine and moonbeams.
实现任何魔术师的愿望
Make any magician's wish come true.
你远道而来
You've come a long way,
比不少无名小卒和过气明星
much further than anyone would have expected
都要长
of a bunch of wanna-hes and has-beans.
过气明星指的是我的话  那我受宠若惊了
If by "has-been" you're referring to me, I just wanna say I'm flattered,
因为我总觉得自己是个无名小卒
because I always considered myself a never-was.
介意我在你身上用一下读心术吗
Do you mind if I do a quick read on you?
当然可以
By all means.
我在构想一个小男孩
Okay, I'm picturing a little boy.
他想成为一个伟大的魔术师
He wants to be a great magician someday.
尽管他很棒，但还是不够好
And though he's good, he's not quite good enough.
最后只能在娱乐圈的底层食物链苟且偷生
So he ends up at the bottom of the entertainment food chain,
以他无法企及的天才吃剩的渣滓为食
feeding off of those who have the talent that he never did.
告诉我 我说得对吗
Tell me. Am I getting close?
等等 在你走之前，我正在研究一个新东西  你有时间吗
Wait. Before you go. I'm working on something new. Do you have a second?
好吧 选一张牌
Okay. Name a card.
红桃K - 知道了
- King of hearts. - Knew it.
在你左边的袖子里  是吗
- It's up your left sleeve. - Is it?
不 我没看到
No. No, I don't see it up there.
你为什么不检查一下你那多余的口袋  就是那个
You know, why don't you check your unnecessary velveteen pocket there?  Yeah
去你的
Suck it.
无论如何 十分感谢您光临寒舍，但这里是非天才免进区域
Anyway, thank you so much for coming by, but this is kind of a talent only area, so...
祝君好运
Break a leg.
祝你也断点什么
Hey, you break something, too.
先生们女士们
Ladies and gentlemen,
Savoy总管欢迎大家
the Savoy management welcomes you
今晚的特别演出
to tonight's special performance,
天启四骑士  第二幕
The Four Horsemen, Act Two.
与传统的表演不一样
Unlike traditional performances,
天启四骑士支持您录影
The Four Horsemen encourage you to film,
打电话给朋友们
call your friends,
上传 在线直播 发微博（Tweet 美国版微博）
upload, stream, and tweet the show freely.
谢谢 演出几分钟后开始
Thank you. The show will begin in a few minutes.
手表不错
Nice watch.
那是传家之宝
It's a family heirloom.
对了  我知道他怎么做到的
By the way, I know how he did that trick.
谁 - Shrike
- Who? - Shrike.
当他才14岁
So, when he was 14,
他看见中心公园 有个树洞
he saw a hole in a tree in Central Park.
他让一名操作旋转木马的工作人员
He had a guy who worked at the carousel
像寻常的把戏那样在牌上签名
sign a card for what looked like a routine little trick.
然后呢
And?
18年后   在那家伙退休时
At the guy's retirement, 18 years later,
Shrike 表演了个节目 让那个人在扑克牌上签字
Shrike performs, has the guy sign a card,
然后-变！
and presto!
牌就到了树上
The card is in the tree.
那牌藏了18年
It was in the tree for 18 years.
牌在树里
The card was in the tree.
这棵树裹卡牌长了18年 那可不是魔术 一点也不魔幻
The tree grew around the card in 18 years. I mean, that isn't magic. It's not magic.
重点是 目光不能短浅
The point is, the trick was not to look closely.
要长远考虑
It was to look so far
要回溯20年去看
that you see 20 years into the past.
Shrike溺水后  他们一直找不到他的尸体
After Shrike drowned, they never found the body.
你在暗示什么
What are you suggesting?
Arthur Tressler为您呈现
Arthur Tressler presents
Jack Wilder
Jack Wilder,
Henley Reeves
Henley Reeves,
Merritt McKinney
Merritt McKinney,
和Daniel Atlas
and Daniel Atlas.
天启四骑士
The Four Horsemen.
谢谢你们 开始之前
Thank you. Before we begin,
我们要特别介绍两个人
we'd like to single out two people in particular.
我们想把今晚的表演送个这位男士和这位女士
A man and a woman to whom we'd like to dedicate tonight's performance.
联邦调查局特工 Dylan Rhodes
FBI Agent Dylan Rhodes
还有可爱，但经验不足的国际刑警Alma dray 各位
and the lovely, if somewhat inexperienced, Interpol Agent Alma Dray, everyone.
对 Rhodes特工可是誓要把我们抓进去的哦
Yeah, Agent Rhodes has personally vowed to "nail us."
如果他机智勇敢的话，就来吧
And we encourage him to do so if he has the brains and the fur.
什么是魔术
What is magic?
要我们说的话 只不过是有针对性是欺骗
Our argument,nothing but targeted deception.
我想让你们看
So I want you to look.
尽可能仔细看
Look as closely as possible.
因为你们接下来看到的把戏
Because the tricks you are about to see
看起来没关系
may not seem connected.
但我们向您保证，他们是有联系的
But we assure you, they are.
接下来进行的到底是100个不同的把戏
Is what follows 100 different tricks?
还是一个巨大的幻觉
Or is it one giant illusion?
现在表演的是书本上最古老的把戏之一
And now for one of the oldest tricks in the book.
Danny 不介意开下箱子吧
Danny, if you wouldn't mind opening up the box,
让大家看看  里面是空的
and showing everybody that it's completely empty.
现在我们需要12名勇敢的志愿者
Now, we're gonna need 12 courageous volunteers.
我们把可爱的毛绒小可爱
I'm gonna take sweet little Fluffy here,
放进去这神秘的盒子里
and put her inside this mystery box.
场内有两只铅笔
There are two pencils out there.
举高点  让我看见
Hold 'em up high. Let me see 'em.
这里 还有这里
- Here! - Yeah!
然后 念出魔咒
And now, you will say the magic word.
Abracadabra
Abracadabra.
对 然后我会挥舞着这根魔杖
Yes, and I will wave this magic wand
没有为什么 然后
for no reason. And then...
毛绒小免就会在我们眼前神奇地消失啦
Fluffy has magically vanished before your very eyes.
如果你们没有经历过集体催眠
If you haven't experienced mass hypnosis,
你即将要体验了
you're about to.
睡
And sleep.
低头 低头 睡 睡 完全睡着
Down, down. Sleep, sleep. Completely sleep.
很好 很好 睡 睡
Good, good. Sleep, sleep.
而今晚我们将要揭开
And now we are gonna debunk
一些魔术秘密
a few magic myths this evening.
我们都知道那兔子是活得好好的
We all know that Fluffy is, in fact, alive and well.
小毛绒就这么奇迹的出现了
And Fluffy has miraculously appeared.
这面镜子
As has the mirror
让这个盒子看起来是空的
which makes the box only appear as though it's empty.
当你听到别动的时候
When you hear the word "freeze"
你们全是橄榄球运动员
you are all football players.
你们要做的事是擒住并摔倒
And your job is to tackle,
大卸八块
dismantle,
死压
crush,
肢解
tear limb from limb,
那个四分卫
the quarterback.
我们都听说过从帽子变出兔子
Now, we've all heard of pulling the rabbit out of the hat.
但有人听过把兔子变成帽子吗
But has anyone heard of pulling a hat out of a rabbit?
你会知道四分卫是谁
You will know who the quarterback is.
他是那个要喊这个词的人
He will be the one saying that word.
"别动"
Freeze.
3 2 1
Three, two, one...
把手放中间 1 2 3
Put your hands in the middle. One, two, three...
干掉四分卫
Kill the quarterback!
回到你们的座位上
Get on back to your seats.
我有感觉我们很快要再次相见
I got a feeling I'm gonna be seeing you soon.
我猜你减肥了吧
I guess you have lost some weight.
中场休息时
At the intermission,
我要你们写下自己现在的银行存款
we asked you to write down your current bank balance,
封在信封里面
and seal it in an envelope.
现在可以拿出信封来
Now it's time to take those envelopes out.
大家拿出来
Everyone take 'em out.
现在 每个人
Now, everybody,
喊出自己的名字 一起来
shout out your name. All at once. Go.
喊出来
Shout 'em out.
Clement? Frannick?
对 在这 真够上
- Yeah! Up here! - Oh. Way up there.
好 Dina? Robertson?
Okay. Dina? Robertson?
是我
That's me!
名字 名字
Okay. Names. Names. Let's go.
Josepha Hickey?
是我
That's me!
Josepha 我要你盯着自己的银行余额
Josepha, I want you to focus on your balance,
大声地从1到10喊出来
and count from one to 10 out loud.
1 2 3 4 5
One, two, three, four, five...
停
Stop.
第一位是5吗
Is the first digit 5?
是的
Yes.
再来一次 这次快点
Do it again. This time, faster.
1 2 3 4 5 6
One, two, three, four, five, six...
停
Stop.
6 继续
Six. Again.
1 2
One, two...
Josepha 你的账户里面余额是562刀吗
Josepha, is your bank balance $562 as of today?
是的 就那么多
Yeah. That's what I got.
不幸的是 你说错了
Unfortunately, you're wrong.
-好的, Dina 1 4 7 7  -对
Okay, Dina,One,Four,Seven,Seven. -Yeah.
你觉得是 但事实上 你也错了
You think it is. But in fact, you, too, are wrong.
Clement
Clement.
你账户里没有6500刀
You do not have $6,500 in your account.
其实 大家站起来 所有人
In fact, everybody stand up. Everybody.
把你们的信封放到额头
Yeah. Put your envelopes to your forehead.
集中注意力想着数字
Focus on your number.
这是 天啊 跟我害怕的一样
This is... Oh, dear. Just as I feared.
这好奇怪
Oh, this is strange.
我不想这么说 但你们都错了
You know, I hate to say this, but you're all wrong.
你们每个人所以为的余额
Every last one of you is dead wrong
全都是错误到家了
about what you think is in your account.
好 你们可以坐下来了
Okay, you can sit down now.
对了 我差点忘了
Yeah. I almost forgot.
如果没有伟大的
This evening would not be possible
赞助人Arthur Tressler 也不会有今晚的演出
if it weren't for our great benefactor Arthur Tressler.
欢迎 掌声
Big applause! Big applause!
Art 你怎么不下来舞台
Art, actually, why don't you come up on stage
进行闭幕表演呢
for the finale?
下来吧 Art
- Come on down, Art! - Come on down, Art!
他来了  好  很好
There he goes. Okay, good.
我们都准备好了吗
Are we on red?
准备就绪  全员待命
Bright red. We're all standing by.
好的 不允许任何人离开剧院  任何人
All right, no one leaves the theater. No one.
他来了
There he goes.
亚瑟 你填了你的信封了吗
Now, Art, did you fill out your envelope?
不用 我们替你写了
Well, no need. We've done it for you.
Art 我猜一下
Now, Art, I took a guess.
超过一亿四千万 对吧
North of 140. Am I right?
那是一亿四千万哦
That's 140 million, by the way.
对不起 Merritt
I'm sorry, Merritt.
为神马只有他的账户余额是对的
How can he be right about his balance
其他人都错了呢
and everyone else be wrong?
我觉得他的可能也是错的
I think possibly because he, too, is wrong.
每个人 拿出纸来
Everybody, take out your paper.
用座位下的手电筒
And using the flashlight under your seat,
开始给纸加温
start to warm up that paper.
你们的正确余额便会显现
I think your correct balance begins to appear.
不要担心  Art 我们给你准备了手电筒
Now, Art, don't worry, we have a flashlight for you.
是的
Yes.
看
Look.
发生了什么  Daniel
What's going on there, Daniel?
等等  好奇怪  一秒前还是
Wait. This is weird. A second ago, it said
$144,579,651
$144,579,651.
但现在
But now...
少了70000刀
Now it says $70,000 less.
Josepha 你能站起来一下吗
Josepha, can you stand up?
好的
Yes.
你的新数字是什么
Now, what is your new number?
我账户里是$70,562
$70,562 now in my account.
Josepha 账户里增加了的钱
Is it possible that Josepha's balance went up
是否可能恰好与亚瑟少了的钱相等
the exact amount that Art's went down?
瞧 又来了
Hey. Check it out. It's happening again.
真的吗
IS it?
真的啊
Wow. It is.
Art的余额又少了28万刀
Art's balance has gone down another 280K.
Dina Robertson 你上面写的是什么呢
Dina Robertson? What did yours say?
$281,477
$281,477.
我们有事要坦白
We have a confession to make.
她是对的 我们说谎了
She's right. We lied about something.
对 你们都不是被随机选中的
Yes. None of you were chosen at random.
你们有个共同点
All of you have one thing in common.
房间里的每个人都是
Everyone in this room was a victim
那一段艰难岁月的受害者
of the hard times that hit one of America's most treasured cities.
有些人失去了房子 车
Some of you lost your houses, your cars.
事业
Your businesses.
爱人
Your loved ones.
但是大家都是向同一家保险公司投保
But all of you were insured by the same company.
Tressler保险公司
Tressler Insurance.
你们被抛弃了
You were abandoned.
你们的安置费
You were loopholed...
被人钻了空子
...out of your settlements.
这只是一场秀 对吗
This is all for show. Correct?
"全都是"指的是我们在台上向买票观众揭露黑幕吗？
"All" meaning we're doing it onstage in front of a paying audience?
是的 那是一场秀
- Then, yes, it's for show. - Whoa! Whoa!
我的账户里有82000刀了
I've got $82,000 in my bank account!
我的手机就这么显示
It says it right here on my cell phone!
大家看看自己的手机 快啊
Everybody, look at your cell phones right now! Everybody!
真的吗
Is this for real?
不知道啊
I don't know.
真的在发生
Is this happening?
不知道 我说不上来
I don't know! I can't tell!
你干的吗
Hey! Did you do this?
我们何德何能  Art
How could we, Art?
我们又没你的密码
We don't have your password.
我们得有
We'd need access to information
我们不可能获得的信息
we could never get our hands on.
对 密保问题  比如
Yes, security questions, for instance, like,
我不知道你妈妈结婚前的名字
I don't know, your mother's maiden name
或是你第一只宠物的名字
or the name of your first pet.
我们是从哪里得到你的信息的   Art
Where would we get that information, Art?
你绝对不可能告诉我们的
You certainly would never tell us.
我们得到确认 真的发生了 他们抢劫了他
We got confirmation. It's really happening. They robbed him.
不要让他们逃走
Do not let them get away.
那飞机和面包卷都还给你留着呢
Hey, we left you the jet and the Rolls.
赔死你个王八蛋
You got hell to pay!
停下
Stop!
停下 都不要动
Stop! Nobody move!
“别动”
Freeze!
他就是四分卫
Quarterback!
我们是天启四骑士
We are The Four Horsemen.
晚安
Good night.
把他们从我身上挪开
Get 'em off me!
滚 滚开
Get off! Get off me!
放开我
Get off me!
好了  所有人都到街上  所有人
All right. I want everyone on the street! Everyone!
四分卫  四分卫
- Quarterback! - Quarterback!
Fuller  在戏剧院门口等我
Fuller, meet me in front of the theater
带上跟踪器
and bring the tracker.
走吧 走吧
Let's go! Let's go! Now! Come on! Let's go!
给我一个跟踪装置
Give me the tracker.
走吧
Let's go.
FBI  让开
FBI! Clear!
迪伦 - 糟糕
- Dylan! - Damn.
你发现了什么
What have you got?
他在这儿 跟着那个红色点
That's him right there. Follow the red dot.
好吧 交给我了 把他们拦住
All right, I'll take this. Go. Box 'em. Cut 'em off that way.
他在Burgundy大街向左转了
He's turning left on Burgundy.
丫的
FUCK!
让开
Hey! Move!
让开 让开
Move! Move!
我发现他在 Bourbon向北移动
I got him heading north on Bourbon.
不好意思 让开 让开
- Sorry. Move, move! - Hey!
Hey, excuse me. Move, move! Excuse me.
・・・BOOB ALERT・・・
我在 Bourbon 跟丢他
I've lost him at Bourbon.
丫的  你在哪
Damn! Where are you?
让开
Excuse me.
他在交易大厅向北移动
He's heading south on Exchange Place.
不要动
Stop!
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
他要进拿破仑宅邸
He's going in Napoleon House.
让开  让开
Move! Move!
让开一条路啊
Move out of the way!
让开
Hey!
Move!
他在洗手间  我抓住他了
He's in the bathroom. I have him in the bathroom.
不要动
Freeze!
放下武器
Lower your weapons!
什么
What?
我在跟踪我自己
I'm tracking myself!
天启四骑士让那些以字母命名的机构
The Horsemen left egg on the face of what they call
无地自容
the alphabet agencies,
让人不禁质问
calling into question
联邦调查局特别小组的能力
the efficacy of the FBI's task force
和此次调查的负责人
as well as the man in charge of the investigation,
特别团员Dylan Rhodes
Special Agent Dylan Rhodes,
受到公众的嘲笑
who was publicly ridiculed,
在今晚甚至被十余名观众扑倒
and even tackled at tonight's performance.
处事笨拙
Talk about a fumble.
这段丑闻可能成为日后人们酒足饭饱的谈资
This is quickly becoming a national story,
这是天启四骑士在数日之内
as The Horsemen have now seemingly pulled off the impossible
第二次完成看似不可能的事
for the second time in as many days.
两天前在维加斯
Two nights ago in Vegas, The Horsemen
天启四骑士似乎抢了巴黎的一家银行
seemingly robbed a bank in Paris...
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我在喝酒
I'm having a drink.
我来接你
I came to get you.
我担心你啊
I'm worried about you.
你在担心我 好吧 我还担心你唉
You're worried about me. Well, I'm worried about you.
Atlas 你抓住他了的
Atlas. You had him.
他没有武器
He didn't have a weapon.
我不能开枪 你懂的
I couldn't shoot him and you know that.
是的 但是 你放走了他
Yeah, but you... You let him go.
是吧
Didn't you?
有个漂亮的法国妞突然出现
A pretty French girl shows up out of the blue,
说是我的搭档  然后放走了坏人
acts like she's my partner and then she lets the bad guy go?
放开我的手臂
Let go of my arm.
你到底是谁
Who exactly are you anyway?
我记得你说过你是坐办公室的
I thought you said you were a desk agent.
身手还不错
Not bad.
这是什么
What is this?
荷鲁斯之眼是什么
What's the Eye of Horus?
没什么 不是今晚该谈的
Oh, certainly nothing I want to get into tonight.
你酒醒的时候已经够轻视我了
You're dismissive enough about me when you're sober.
自己回家吧
Find your way back yourself.
Bradley先生 Tressler先生想请你与其共饮
Mr. Bradley? Mr. Tresslerwould like you to join him for a drink.
先生
Sir.
谢了
Thank you.
你在他们中扮演什么角色
What is your role with them?
角色
Role?
是 你看上去知道他们所有事
Yes. You seem to know everything about them.
他们会做什么 他们会去哪儿
What they're gonna do. Where they're gonna be.
如果能让你好过点
If it makes you feel any better,
我会说这与你无关
this wasn't about you.
那你告诉我为神马与我无关
Please tell me why this was not about me.
这只是魔术 Tressler
This is a magic trick, Mr. Tressler.
全球规模的
Played out on a global scale.
而你 先生…你只是他们的abracadabra （魔咒，暗指 棋子）
You, sir, are the abracadabra.
是他们偷梁换柱时用来分散注意力的
The distraction, while they set up the real trick.
用我1亿4千万来分散注意力？
I was a $140-million distraction?
是的
Yes.
那种非常自我使你第一时间融入他们
And that very ego that got you involved with them in the first place
这让你看不到这一切
is what keeps you from seeing that.
你知道  "我可以让你永远翻不了身"
- You know... -"I can destroy you."
我知道
Yes, I do know.
你不会的
Well, you won't.
你也不会让他们不得翻身
And you won't destroy them.
无论这大戏法是什么
Whatever this grand trick is,
都是老早就设计好的
it was designed a long time ago.
我相信接下来的才是真正令人惊叹的好戏
And I believe that what's about to follow is really going to amaze.
所以我建议放松 好好享受你的前座
So I suggest you sit back and enjoy your front row seat.
你可是为它花了好多钱
You paid quite a lot of good money for it.
无论你赚了多少
Whatever you stand to make
我出两倍 如果你现在就能揭发他们
I'll double it, if you expose them now.
摧毁他们
And destroy them.
我挣了500万
I stand to make five million.
你看我退缩了吗
Am I flinching?
不 你没有
No, you're not.
不好意思抓疼了你的手臂
I'm sorry for your arm.
不 是我不好意思
No. I'm sorry.
我是个混蛋 我醉了
I was an asshole. I was drunk.
我不知所措
I'm at a loss.
Merritt告诉我 我几乎整天呆在办公室 他是对的
You know, when Merritt said I hardly spent any time away from the desk, he was right.
我是一个调查员 我最擅长那个
I'm a researcher. That's what I do best.
那这怎么回事
So what's this all about?
据说  如果你相信的话
Supposedly, if you buy into it,
目行者是真正魔术
The Eye are the keepers
的看守者
of real magic
以及所有魔术师的保护神
and the protectors of those who practice it.
候选人应该遵循
"Candidates for initiations
必须谨记并绝对服从以下命令
"must follow a series of commands with blind obedience."
荒诞不经 但还有很多人相信这个
- This isn't real. - But there are some who think it is.
我来
May I?
据这本书上所说  他们一个世纪才挑两次人
According to this, they only take new people twice a century.
那又怎么样 那些魔术师做这些就是为了成为目行者一员
So what? The Horsemen are doing these shows in order to get into this thing?
我不知道  我不知道
- I don't know. - I don't know.
我的意思是他们本可以直接抢银行
I mean, I guess these guys could just rob banks to rob banks.
用不着表演
They don't have to put on a show for that.
这可能只是神话
It's probably just a myth.
但前后却说不通，而且我觉得这事不能按寻常逻辑思考
But it doesn't make any sense, and I don't think logic will solve this for us.
我现在也这么想了 - 没错
- You don't say? - No.
我相信有些事情
Ibefieve that some things are only discovered
只有离得足够远才能看清某些东西
if you take certain leaps.
好了  我要    是啊
- Well, I gotta get to... - Yeah. Yeah.
谢谢 晚安 - 嗯 晚安
- Thanks. Good night. - Yeah. Good night.
不好意思 - 没关系
- Sorry. -It's all right.
如果目行者存在 我们得假设他们正在看着我们 对吧
If The Eye did exist, we'd have to assume they were watching us, right?
该死
Shit.
我觉得有人在监视我们 但这不是魔术
I think someone is watching us, but it isn't magic.
你的担心没错 这不是你的手机
Your fears are correct. This is not and has never been your phone.
复制出来的 一模一样
It's a clone in every way, except for this.
漏洞
A bug.
有人监视了所有电话和短信
Someone has heard every call, read every text.
他们就是这样领先我们一步的
That's how they were able to stay ahead of us.
该死的
God damn it!
让我看看Atlas的审讯监控视频
Get me Atlas' interrogation tape.
好的 我硬盘上有
Yes, sir. I have it on the hard drive.
播放图像
Picture's up.
快进
Okay, fast forward.
快进 快进 停
Go on, go on. Freeze!
一帧一帧来
Okay. Frame by frame. Go on.
正常播放
Play it through.
停 放大 再放大
Stop. Zoom in tighter. Tighter.
这里 他拿了我的手机
There. That's where he took my phone.
这个东西还在传送吗
Is that thing transmitting?
只有你在打电话发短信的时候
Only when you're making a call or sending a text.
我把那个窃听器摘除了
Plus I removed the bug.
放回去 开机
All right. Put it back in and turn on the phone.
他们还不知道我们已经发现了窃听器
They don't know that we know about the bug.
从现在开始  我们领先他们一步了
As of this instant, we are ahead of them.
我们要这样保持下去 了解吗
We need to keep it that way. Understand?
找到我的手机  跟踪它
Find my real phone and track it.
已经搞定了  20分钟之前在纽约市
Already did. As of about 20 minutes ago, it's in New York City.
很好
Good.
我要来个半渡击之
I wanna cut 'em off at the knees.
他们有电  切断
They got power? Cut it.
电话  电 水 统统切断
They got phones, electricity, water? Cut it.
把他们榨干
Squeeze 'em out.
感觉我们的存在
I want 'em to feel our presence.
给我弄架直升机
And get me an airplane!
防火墙挂了 他们知道吗
The firewall's down. Do they know about this?
谁
They who?
他们  我们为其效力的人
"They," "them," whoever we're working for.
我们替谁卖命
Who are we working for?
我们要为他们进监狱吗
And are we prepared to go to jail for them?
不要傻了
Stop being paranoid.
确有其事
It really does happen.
你进过监狱 不代表我们也会
It happened to you. Doesn't mean it's gonna happen to us.
伙计 我不造我能不能做成这件事
Guys, I don't know if can do this, all right.
我不想进监狱 你知道吗
I don't want to go to jail, you know?
那就不要搞砸了 你老是说
Then don't screw up. You're always talking about
你想被当做成年人对待吗
wanting to be treated like an adult.
现在是你拿出成年人样子的时候了
Now might be a good time to start acting like one.
按照计划行事 留在这儿 全烧了
Stick to the plan. Stay here and burn it all.
我不知道我在这儿干嘛的
I don't know what I'm doing here.
我也不知道你在其它地方还能干嘛
I don't know what you would do anywhere else.
我来这是为了 彩虹末端的那一桶金（引用西方传说）
I'm here for the pot of gold at the end of the rainbow.
拿到我就跑
That's it. Then I'm gone.
结束后你想干什么就干什么  Merritt
You can do whatever you want when this is over, Merritt.
在那之前 你要按照计划行事
But until then, you stick to the plan.
伙伴们 他们来了
Hey, guys. They're here.
我们的人准备好了 速战速决
- My guys are ready to go. - Let's do this quickly...
不 什么
- No. - What?
她不具有管辖权
She doesn't have jurisdiction here.
她是国际刑警 跟我一起的
She's Interpol. She's with me.
她留在这里
She stays.
什么？什么？
What? What?
呆在车里
Stay in the car.
我们走吧
Let's go.
好了 开干
Okay. Let's do it.
联邦调查局
FBI
女士优先
Ladies first.
不要动
Don't move!
告诉我
Tell me.
我的钱花的值吗
Is my money being well-spent?
当然值
Exceedingly well.
那你告诉我
Now you tell me,
你要怎么处置这些骑士
how do you like your Horsemen?
炖了还是炸了？
Fricasseed or fried?
碎了
Shredded.
我会告诉厨师的
I'll tell the Chef.
别动
Freeze!
Dylan
Dylan!
坚持住
Hold on!
你这小…
You little...
来这儿
Come here!
5楼无情况 向六楼转移
Five is clear. Standing by for six.
你这小混蛋
You little Shit!
你在搞什么 你在搞什么
- What game are you playing? - What game are you playing?
我们在6楼没什么情况  上7楼
We're all good at six. Move to seven.
收到 上7楼  上 上
Copy that. Going to seven. Go, go, go!
不 不 回来
No, no, no, no, no. Go back!
来这儿
Come here!
快来这儿
好的 等等 等等
All right, hold on, hold on!
不是吧  就是
-Really? -Yup.
你这小(混蛋)
You little b...
该死
Shit!
把那给我
Give me that!
所有单位 封锁北边出口
All units, cover the north exit now!
Evan收到
Clear on Evan.
封锁所有可能的出口
Block every possible exit.
回来 丫的
Hey! Get back. Shit.
FBI 算是吧 我征用你的车，谢谢 - 什么？
- FBI. Sort of. I need your car. Thanks. - What?
什么
What?
停车 停车
Stop!Stop!
停下来
好的 跟住他
Good. Follow him!
别叫我留在车里  永远别
Don't ever tell me to stay in the car. Ever.
又不是我命令
I didn't have tactical command.
如果你不信任我 直说
If you don't trust me, just tell me.
向我保证 下次 你会支持我
Promise me, next time, you will back me up.
我们能不能待会再说
Could we have this conversation later, please?
不
No!
好吧 我答应你 现在快开车
Okay, fine, I promise. Now, go!
他们去哪了  他们去哪了
- Where'd they go? - Where are they?
我不造 她开了某人的车
I don't know. She just took some guy's car.
他们在哪？ 那边 那边
- Where are they? - That way. That way.
这是你的车？ 嗯
- Is that your car? - Yeah.
我们走
Let's go.
他在那
There he is!
闪开
Move!
左转
Left!
我们在佛兰基罗斯福路向东
We're heading east on the FDR Drive.
这不是东 - 向北  向北
- This is not east. - North! North!
我们正向北开往罗斯福路  搞什么
- We're heading north on the FDR Drive. - What?
我们在罗斯福路上方为您发来现场报道
We're coming to you live above the FDR,
如你所见 纽约市警察和联邦探员
where NYPD and federal agents, as you now see,
都参与了这次竞速追逐
are engaged in a high-speed pursuit,
跟在黑色轿车后面
following a black sedan.
Fuller  你在哪？
Fuller, where are you?
不远 紧跟你们
Right here. Trying to catch up to you now.
我们正在试着找一个好位置取景
We're now trying to get you a better shot.
再给力点
Come on.
不好意思
Sorry.
看来他们正开往
It looks like they're turning
第59号街 大桥了
onto the 59th Street Bridge.
只要他们还在我们的视线中
As soon as we have them within range,
我们就会为您带来现场直播
we will bring you those pictures live.
好的  跟好了
Good. Just stay with him.
上 上 上
Go, go, go!
后面 你在巴士后面
Behind... You're behind the bus!
超车
Get over!
糟糕
Oh, shit!
出来
Come here!
后退  后退
Get back! Get back!
Dylan 走吧 兄弟  快走
Dylan, let's go, man!Come on,you.
兄弟 出来啊 他会死在里面的
- Come on, man! Get out! - He's gonna die in here.
不要管他 你做不了什么的
Leave him! There's nothing you can do!
我们走 不要管他了
Let's go! Leave him!
文件 -  Dylan
'The Paper! - Dylan!
我们走 我们走 快点
Let's go! Let's go! Come on!
今天 饱受褒奖和争议的魔术团体
Today, the unfolding story of a popular and controversial group of magicians,
把唐人街的警方展开的缉拿行动
who have been fast capturing the public's imagination,
变为一场在第59街大桥展开的
took a dark turn when a police action that began in Chinatown
戏剧性高速追捕行动
developed into a dramatic, high-speed chase across the 59th Street Bridge,
导致天启四骑士之一的Jack Wilder
which caused a fatal collision that took the life of Jack Wilder,
在汽车爆炸中不幸罹难
one of the so-called Four Horsemen.
到目前为止 其余三名成员仍不知所踪
The whereabouts of the other three Horsemen remain unknown at this time.
Dylan 他们刚刚调查了Jack车上的文件了
Dylan, they just figured out what the paper was in Jack's car.
所以他们有什么发现吗
So they know what it is?
知道 到底那小子为什么誓死保护它
And why the kid died trying to protect it.
Evans会尽快让我们知道的
Evans is on his way to brief us right now.
我们走吧
Let's go.
你得先接这个电话
You're gonna wanna take this first, though.
谁的
What's that?
你的朋友Thaddeus Bradley
Your friend Thaddeus Bradley.
Rhodes
Rhodes.
你知道魔术师助手的作用
You do understand the function
对吧  Rhodes探长
of the magician's assistant, don't you, Agent Rhodes?
当魔术师负责耍把戏时
Yeah, she's there to distract them
助手来分散观众注意力
while he sets up the trick.
你错的还不太算离谱
You'd be right if you weren't so wrong.
当你关注魔术师时
While you're watching the magician,
那一脸无辜的小可爱却在操控一切
that lovely innocent is actually pulling the strings.
难道你不觉得派个做文员的国际刑警
Don't you find it peculiar that Interpol would send you
来当你的助手很奇怪吗
a first timer off the desk to be your assistant?
为什么她会加入到这个案子来
Why did she request to be put on the case?
她被委派的
She was assigned to the case.
抽到好牌了
Luck of the draw.
就像从牌堆里随机抽牌一样
Like choosing a random card in the deck.
我觉得你突然间的好心更奇怪
I find it odd, your sudden act of generosity.
你在打什么小算盘
What's in it for you?
我只是想让游戏更公平
Just trying to even the game.
我觉得我是在和绑了沙袋 戴了脚蹼的人斗
I feel like I'm playing with somebody wearing ankle weights and flippers.
加油  Rhodes探员 加油
Keep up, Agent Rhodes. Keep up.
我们有麻烦了
We got a problem.
这有个保险箱  不 不 不
Here's the safe.No,no,no.Hey.
他在那干嘛
What's he doing here?
给我们可靠的切入点
Giving us our first solid lead.
我们在调查一个私人保安承包商
We've been investigating a private security contractor
叫名Elkhorn
called Elkhorn
在过去5年 肿么了
-for the last five years. - And?
他们匿藏了将近5亿美金
They've been hiding close to a half billion dollars...
我没问你 我问他
I didn't ask you. I asked him.
钱被放在皇后区的一个仓库的保险箱里
The money's in a vault inside a warehouse in Queens.
我认为保险箱是魔术师的终极目标
We think this vault is your magicians' final target.
桥上死的魔术师…
The magician who died on the bridge...
你从他手里拿出的绝密文件正是Elkhorn公司的
You pulled our classified Elkhorn file right from his crispy little hand.
除了那些像罗宾汉的花招
And despite their bullshit Robin Hood razzle-dazzle,
那帮魔术师和普通盗贼没什么两样
your magicians are nothing more than common thieves.
他们是怎么拿到文件的
How did they get the file?
我保证这部分
This is the part you're gonna find
才是你最感兴趣的 Rhodes探员
particularly interesting, Agent Rhodes.
当他们在新奥尔良
They patched to my server after they accessed
进入你手机的指挥中心后
your mobile command center in New Orleans
从你那儿盗取了服务器的密码
with codes they got from your phone.
你当时命令我们全部去追捕
You ordered us all out to chase after them.
你们在这个案子上所展现的无能程度
The level of incompetence displayed on this case,
本身就是个魔术了
that's a magic trick in and of itself.
Abracadabra 我要接手这案子
Abracadabra. I'm taking over.
老板 他接手？
Boss, he's taking over?
我们走吧先生们
Let's go, gentlemen.
我想和你谈谈
Hey. I want to have a word with you.
以后不要像个刚才那样和我说话
Don't ever talk to me like that again.
你究竟为什么要接这个案子 什么？
- Why the hell did you take this case? - What?
美国人有句话“知人口面不知心”
People say I'm "hard to read." That's an American expression.
你懂吗
Do you understand it?
是的
Yes.
那好 现在我就跟你讲清楚
Good, then let me make myself perfectly clear to you.
如果我发现你除了做现在的工作外
If I find out that you are anything other than
还搞些小动作的话  我发誓我会..
who you say you are, I swear...
我们法国也有一句话
And we French also have an expression.
信念可以移山
La foi soulève la montagne.
即信任能战胜一切
"Faith can move mountains."
如果我们想抓住魔术师
If we hope to capture The Horsemen,
你就要对我有信任之心
then you need to have a little faith in me.
因为我没做见不得人的事
Because I've done nothing to deserve otherwise.
我刚刚就被人出卖了
I just got my ass handed to me.
这个案子不归我管了
I am losing this case.
现在信任这种奢侈我可享受不起
So faith is a luxury I don't have any time for right now.
在他生命中，比任何东西更重要的是
More than anything in his life,
Jack想成为史上最有名的魔术师
Jack wanted to be the most famous magician who ever lived.
我无法说他实现了梦想
And I can't say he achieved it,
但是我希望无论在哪 都充满魔术
but I do hope wherever he is, it is full of magic.
关键是  抱歉
But the point is... Sorry.
关键是
The point is...
关键是我们之所以在这儿是想说我们现在不能放弃
The point of why we are here is to say that we are not... We cannot quit now.
我们已经开始实施了更大的计划
We've started something bigger than all of us.
我们一定要去完成它
We have to finish it.
接近仓库
Approaching the warehouse.
5 6小组负责南北面出口
Units 5 and 6 cover the north and south entrances.
我们正去往保险箱所在地
We are going for the vault.
保险箱呢  保险箱呢
Hey. Where's the safe? Where's the safe?
什么情况？
What is this?
那该死的保险箱去哪儿了
Where the hell is the goddamn safe?
你们在外面的时候 我们搬走了啊
We just moved it while you were outside.
Evans的命令  什么
- Evans' orders. - What?
我可没说过啊
I never said that.
长官 你之前打过电话
Sir, you got a phone call
说华盛顿想搬离保险箱
and said Washington wants the safe moved.
你没有听我亲口说出这些吧 探员
You never heard that come out of my mouth, Agent.
什么情况
What happened?
告诉我怎么了 你们简直在瞎扯淡
You tell me what's going on, because this is bullshit!
不
No!
我的神啊
Jesus Christ.
长官 长官  你在干什么
Sir? Sir? What are you doing?
我觉得是贝多芬的D大调协奏曲
I think it's Beethoven's Concerto in D-Major.
保险箱在哪里
Where's the safe?
他们手下在装箱
His team is loading the truck.
拦住货车 拦住
- Stop the truck! - Stop!
拦 拦住货车啊
- Stop! - Hey! Stop that truck!
怎么回事 上头有命令
What the hell's going on? We got our orders.
你现在有新命令了 打开它
Now you've got new orders. Open it up.
好吧 现在听我的
Okay. Here's what I want.
这会儿 他们以为保险箱已经离开这儿了
At this moment, they think that safe's leaving this site.
我们将计就计
So we stay with it.
跟着它一直到 这是送到哪？
We follow it all the way to... Where's it going?
Pointz街5号
5 Pointz. Up the street.
那我们去Pointz街5号 保险箱去哪我们就去哪
So we go to 5 Pointz. Wherever the safe goes, we go.
它会带我们去找他们
It'll lead us right to 'em.
你们两个跟着我
You two are with me.
伙伴们
Guys.
看 局里面来让我们看看介个
Look. Office just called with this.
骑士们20分钟之前把它上传到YouTube
Horsemen posted it to YouTube 20 minutes ago.
我们之所以在这儿 就是想说我们不会
The point of why we're here is to say that we are not...
放弃 且不能放弃
We cannot quit now.
我们已经开始实施更伟大的计划
We've started something bigger than all of us.
我们必须完成它
We have to finish it.
当你们看表演时 记住Jack Wilder 的名字
Remember the name Jack Wilder when you see us live,
我们七点相约在皇后区 Pointz街五号
5 Pointz, Queens, 7:00.
表演还有半个小时开始
Their show is in a half an hour.
这正是我们要去的地方
It's exactly where we're headed.
我不确定 老大 我不想唱反调
I don't know, boss. I don't wanna be the naysayer,
但是这帮家伙真的很狡猾
but these guys are kinda tricky.
Rhodes  他们只不过是几个艺人
Rhodes, they're entertainers.
人群涌向皇后区 Pointz街五号
A stunning turnout here in 5 Pointz
之前逃脱的骑士们将会给FBI最后一记耳光
as the renegade Horsemen taunt the FBI into a final showdown.
天启四骑士邀请我们参与
The Horsemen have invited us to their final round
和FBI展开的三轮对决的最后一轮
of their three-act face-off with the FBI.
他们到底留了哪一手  我们拭目以待
What do they have in store? We're about to find out.
盯着货车 看一下谁在靠近的
All eyes on the truck. Let's see who approaches.
收到
Copy that.
Rhodes探长？Fuller
Agents Rhodes, Fuller?
有什么新情况
Go, for us.
这儿有情况 有人走向货车
We've got movement. Someone's walking toward the truck.
是个女人
It's a woman.
别动 - 糟糕
- Freeze! - Oh, shit!
到底怎么回事
What the hell's going on?
是电视上那家伙
Hey! It's the guy from the TV.
把枪放下
Put your guns down.
看啊这是谁 第五位骑士
Look who it is. The fifth Horseman.
你逗我玩呢
Are you kidding?
我在跟踪他们 就像你一样
I'm following them, just like you are.
我没有跟踪任何人
I'm not following anybody anymore.
你一直以来都赶在我们前面
You've been ahead of us this whole time.
但这次 我比你领先一步
But guess what? I'm ahead of you now.
你束手就擒吧
Your ass is mine.
你们这群白痴
You guys are still idiots.
这儿碰巧是
This happens to be the former
Lionel Shrike生前排练的场地
rehearsal space for Lionel Shrike.
也是我第一场表演的地方
It's where I did my first show.
如果你还想接着出丑的话
Now, if you wanna look like even bigger idiots,
就打开保险箱
why not open it?
当你们这么做时 Rhodes探员
And while you're doing it, Agent Rhodes,
介不介意再做一次那种
would you mind reenacting your look
无比困惑的表情吗
of absolute befuddlement for me?
用它做我DVD封面再好不过了
It will make a wonderful cover for my DVD.
打开保险箱
Open the safe.
去  打开它
- Go ahead. - Open it.
什么鬼
What the hell?
什么
What?
把它给我
Give me that.
不
No.
No!
这什么情况
What is this?
后退
Get back!
谁不喜欢精彩的魔术表演呢
Who doesn't love a good magic trick?
他们又让你跟一个空的保险箱跑
They have you chasing empty safes again.
又一次 误导
Once again, misdirection.
表演马上要开始了  准备行动
The show is starting. Move out!
Rhodes探长 我想问的是
The question I'd be asking now, Agent Rhodes is,
真的保险箱到底在哪
"What happened to the real one?"
让路 让他们让开
Clear! Clear 'em out!
快让他们让开 别挡路
Come on. Move 'em out. Move 'em out of the way.
FBI  给我们让开
FBI! Give me a path!
让开  让开
Clear out! Clear out!
魔术是什么
What is magic?
魔术是错觉
Magic is deception.
但是错觉是为了给人带来快乐
But deception designed to delight,
娱乐和灵感
to entertain, to inspire.
当心 让开 让开 当心
Look out! Clear! Clear! Look out!
魔术是一种信仰
It is about belief.
信念
Faith.
信任
Trust.
没有那些品质
Without those qualities,
魔术作为一种艺术形式 将会名存实亡
magic, as an art form, would no longer exist.
但是如果这些品质
But what happens if these qualities
不是用于崇高理想
are not used for their higher purpose?
而是用来欺骗、撒谎
And instead they're used to cheat, lie.
为了一己私欲和欲壑难填的贪婪
For personal gain or for greed.
这就不再是魔术了
Then it's no longer magic.
而是犯罪
It's crime.
所以今夜 为了我们的闭幕演出
So tonight, for our final act,
你们要帮我们拨乱反正
you're gonna help us set a few things right.
这里什么情况  Rhodes
What's going on here, Rhodes?
我不清楚
I don't know.
演出开始
Showtime.
看
Look!
他们在房顶上面 快行动
There they are on the roof. Let's move!
走 走 走
Go, go, go!
Dylan！ - FBI  闪开
- Dylan! - FBI, coming through!
你在这儿干什么？
What are you doing here?
他们走错方向了
They're going in the wrong direction
你心里清楚
and you know it.
Rhodes 全员行动 快点
Rhodes! I need all personnel now!
你要相信我 坚定你的信念
You need to trust me. Take your leap of faith.
等一下
Wait.
我要和她一起去
I'm going to go with her.
去吧  我支持你  我一会就回来
Go. I got your back. I'll be right here.
去吧
Go ahead!
Fuller 出事你负责
That's on you, Fuller.
上 上 上
Let's go, let's go! Now, now, now!
Daniel
Daniel?
怎么了
Yeah?
这么说吧 我们这一年的冒险生活
As our, let's call it, year of living dangerously
马上就要结束了
comes to a close, in a rare moment of vulnerability,
我想为我们的友谊说几句真心话
I'd like to express a sentiment about our relationship.
好吧
Okay.
我第一次见到你 我觉得你是个
Well, when I first met you, I thought you were kind of a
混蛋
dick.
然后呢
And?
没有然后 就这样
No, that's it.
很好
That's very nice.
我好感动
- Yeah. - I'm touched.
这可是发自内心的
Yeah. Just from the heart.
我可没说我哪里感动了
Well, I didn't tell you where I was touched.
你丫的
Oh, you!
天啊 一切结束后我们又何去何从
Oh, God. What are we gonna do when this is over?
自力更生
We're on our own.
我们的得到的指示只写到这次表演结束
Our instructions run out after the show.
即使没有目行者
Even if there is no "Eye,"
即使我们被耍的团团转
if we were completely played and we spend
还是要蹲20年的监狱
the next 20 years in jail, then,
我只是想说…
I just want to say that...
我知道 我也一样
I know. Me, too.
我可吃不消你们这么煽情
Little too sentimental for me.
他们在那
There they are!
去抓他们 上 上
Go grab 'em! Put 'em down! Go, go, go!
去抓人
Grab 'em!
起来
Get up!
什么情况
What the hell?
该死
Shit!
你好 纽约
Hello, New York!
感谢魔术
Thank you for the magic.
同时感谢你们这些
And thank you for being such
伟大而忠实的观众
an incredible and dedicated audience.
但是  天下没有不散的宴席
Unfortunately, like all good things,
这必须要结束
it must come to an end.
所以我们今晚的表演以
So we would like to start our show tonight...
用告别来开场
By saying goodbye.
我们想要的
All we wanted was to
是向世界展示一场魔术表演
bring the world to a magic show.
也以此给世界带来一点魔力
And thereby bring a little magic
让开啊
Clear the way!
这一路我们走的很艰辛
This has been one hell of a ride for all of us.
是我们消失的时候了
But it's time for us to disappear.
晚安 纽约
Good night, New York.
谢谢你的信任
And thank you for believing in us.
停
Stop!
不
No!
尼玛
God damn it!
对不起
I'm sorry.
你是对的 这比我们大家都重要
You were right. It's bigger than all of us.
这次我虽然对了但我并不因此开心
This is one time I'm not happy being right.
我猜就是的
So I guess this is it.
是吗
IS it?
Dylan Dylan Dylan
Dylan!Dylan!Dylan!
你看看  这是什么
- You see that? - What?
那真的钱在哪里啊
Where's the real money?
你被捕了 手举起来
You're under arrest! Hands in the air! Now!
我被陷害了
I've been framed.
我也觉得
I'm sure you were.
我一贯可以
Yeah, but I can prove it.
我真的可以
I always do.
就像我一直预言你会干蠢事一样
Just like I predicted that you'd play the fool.
我们就不要谈这些戏剧性的东西了
Let's just drop the theatricality, all right?
又不是在拍电影
The cameras aren't rolling in here.
伙伴们 我能单独跟这位朋友谈谈吗
Fellas, can I have a few minutes with my friend here alone, please.
当然
Sure.
好的
All right.
我有信息可以提供给你
I got information to trade.
然后就能放我走吧
I believe that's how it's done. Huh?
除非物有所值
If it's of some value.
牢狱生活给了一个人思考的时间
These bars give a man time to think.
我确保我知道他们是怎么办的
And I'm pretty sure I know how they did it.
还记得第二场里面的兔子魔术吗
Remember the rabbit trick in the second show?
这盒子可不是空的
The box was never empty.
房间也不是
The room wasn't either.
进入仓库后
After gaining access to the warehouse,
骑士们将真的保险箱留在原地
The Horsemen left the real safe
把整个房间变成了大号兔子箱
and transformed the whole room
巨大的兔子盒子
into a giant rabbit box.
你们就这么冲进去
You go charging in there,
以为保险箱早不见了
thinking the safe was already gone.
又被耍了
Missing the trick. Again.
让你误以为
Which was to make you think
保险箱已经被偷了
the safe had already been stolen,
所以你放松警惕就离开了
so you'd drop your guard and leave.
当你正在那儿忙着玩动物型气球
Now, while you were busy playing with balloon animals,
有人闯入了仓库
someone was breaking into the warehouse.
谁
Who?
Jack Wilder
Jack Wilder.
天啊
Holy shit.
怎么可能 他就死在我的眼皮底下
No. No way. He died right in front of my eyes.
除非 当然 他没死
Unless, of course, he didn't.
门锁着的
It's locked.
我不是说过吗
Weren't you listening?
没有东西永远会锁着的
Nothing's ever locked.
干得好  Wilder  干得好
Well done, Mr. Wilder! Good work.
你是个大男孩了 Jack
You're a big boy now, Jack.
他开了一辆FBI的车跑了 对吧
He escaped in a standard FBI vehicle, right?
引你到桥那边
Led you to the bridge.
其他骑士已经在那儿等着
Where the other Horsemen were waiting
还带着一辆一模一样的备用车
with an identical replacement car.
只需花几秒钟
It only took a split second
就可以让你跟丢
for you to lose contact with it
然后进行调换
and make the switch.
当你爬进去那部燃烧着的汽车
When you crawled into that burning car,
你的举动特英勇 不得不说
quite heroically, I might add,
你冒着生命危险去尝试
you almost died trying to rescue
去救一具停尸房里的尸体
what I assume was a cadaver from the morgue.
为什么要实施这么一处天衣无缝又危机四伏的计划
Why go through such an elaborate and dangerous plan
就为了陷害一个人呢
just to frame one guy?
我不明白
I don't know.
他们从不拿所取之财
They never kept any of the money they took.
对这个问题还没有答案
Yeah, that's the part I haven't been able to put together yet.
但是我给了你更加实质性的重要信息
But I just gave you information that is substantially more important.
不 其实没有 - 什么
- No. Not really. - What?
我后来有机会好好调查一下Lionel Shrike
I finally got a chance to really look into Lionel Shrike.
弄出他的复出意图和那次事故的缘由
His comeback attempt. His accident.
拒绝支付家属赔偿的保险公司
The insurer who denied the family's claim?
就是Tressler保险公司
Tressler Insurance.
那个拥有相关票据的银行？
The bank that carried the note?
也正是巴黎信贷共和银行
Credit Republican of Paris.
巴黎信贷共和银行
Credit Republicain de Paris.
你怎么解释
What do you make of that?
魂淡时时有
A sucker is born every minute.
我们凌晨两点被引到
What if all this was just leading up to
中央公园 万一被打劫了怎么办
us getting mugged in Central Park at 2:00 a.m.?
不会的  我们正是需要来这里
No, I'm telling you, we're right where we need to be.
只需要找…
We just have to find...
那个?
That?
Lionel Shrike之树
The Lionel Shrike tree.
还有封在玻璃瓶内的纸牌
And the card encased in glass.
我们现在怎么做？
What do we do now?
酷
Oh, nice!
我现在换种想法
So, here's my new theory.
传说中的目行者无处不在
The legend is that the "Eye" is everywhere.
等待
Waiting
真正伟大的魔术师将自己与平凡之辈
for the truly great magicians to distinguish themselves
区分开来
from the mediocre ones.
也许你就是其中一员
Maybe that was you.
内心深处 你强烈渴望成为
Deep down inside you wanted nothing more
想成为一名目行者 却从来被邀请
than to be part of the "Eye," but you were never invited.
所以你企图摧毁他们 但是事与愿违
So you try to destroy them. But instead what happens?
你惹毛了他们
You pissed them off.
目行者不存在
The Eye isn't real.
好 那你解释一下 谁在幕后指使
Okay, then, explain then. Who's behind all this?
某个丧心病狂
Somebody with an obsession.
拘泥小节的人 谁
- Meticulous. - Who?
准备牺牲一切的人
Somebody prepared to sacrifice everything.
如此孤注一掷以至于
Somebody so prepared to lose
他在花招耍完之前都不会被怀疑
that they wouldn't even be a suspect until the trick was done.
我不要模糊对象 我要名字 是谁
I don't want a profile. I need a name. Who? Who?
我不知道
I don't know who.
但是他们一定是进入仓库
But they had to have access to the warehouse
安好镜子
to plant the mirrors.
总是领先我一步 还有美国联邦调查局
Always a step ahead of me. And the FBI.
不是一次 两次 而是总是
Got past them not once, not twice, but consistently.
就像他们
Almost as if they were on the...
就潜伏在里面
The inside.
你
You.
为神马
Why?
就是这个问题 不是吗
That is the question, isn't it?
你说得对
You're right.
我不能告诉你我等了多久
I can't tell you how long I've waited
就为了看你脸上的表情
to see the look on your face.
你是谁？
Who are you?
你想在我身上要什么
What do you want from me?
我想要什么
What do I want?
我想看你在这个牢房里度过余生
I want you to spend the rest of your life in this cell,
盯着四面墙 反省下你的所作所为
staring at four walls and wondering how you missed it.
是如何因自负而被蒙蔽了双眼
How you let yourself be so blinded by your ego
自以为自己领先了一步
that you convinced yourself that you were one step ahead
事实上你却总是落后两步
when you were always two steps behind.
Dylan？
Dylan?
等一下
Wait a minute.
Dylan 这到底怎么回事
Dylan! How did this happen?
Dylan
Dylan!
为神马？
Why?
哦 上帝
Oh, my God.
不是真的吧
I did not see that coming.
这不科学啊
That's impossible!
不可能啊
No way.
那其实不错
That was actually pretty good.
谢谢
Thank you.
当我说 一定要做房间里最聪明的人
When I said, "Always be the smartest guy in the room."
我们意见一致
We were in agreement.
那就好
Okay. Right.
亨利
Henley.
我没见过她说不出话来的时候
I've never seen her speechless.
我把这话当做夸我了
I take that as a huge compliment.
真是不好意思 之前揍了你一顿
Hey, man, I'm so sorry for kicking your ass. Really.
听着 正经的
Hey, listen, for the record,
我从来都百分百相信魔术
I have always been a 100% believer.
而且我还为此花了不少精力
And the amount of energy I have expended to keep
让这些不信的人去相信
these infidels on point...
Merritt 你可以加入了
Merritt, you're in.
上帝保佑
God bless.
来
Come.
真正的魔术是让四位强大的个人
The real magic is taking four strong solo acts
组成队且并肩合作
and making them all work together.
而你们正是这样做的
And that's exactly what you did.
欢迎
So welcome.
欢迎加入目行者
Welcome to the Eye.
困死在水牢中
重现伟大魔术失败 Shrike消失在河里
大型魔术成为Shrike的致命闭幕演出 搜救队找不到其遗体
这都有联系的
It was all connected.
信贷共和银行  Tressler保险公司
Credit Republican. Tressler Insurance.
-你好  -你好
-Bonjour.  -Bonjour.
Elkhorn 呢
And Elkhorn?
这和Shrike什么关系
What's the connection to Shrike?
Elkhorn最初是保险柜生产商
Elkhorn started as a safe manufacturer.
他们用廉价的钢材
They used cheap steel.
吃回扣
They cut corners.
当Shrike下沉到河底的时候 保险箱变形了
When he got to the bottom of the river, the safe warped.
他被困住了
And he was trapped.
他是你的父亲
He was your father.
演出前的早晨我就觉得有些异样
The morning before the show didn't feel like any other day.
当我父亲说要去工作 他看得出来我不想让他走
When my father said he had to go to work, he could see that I didn't want him to leave.
所以他把他的手表给我 要我一直数着秒针等他回来
So he gave me his watch, and he told me to count the seconds until he came back.
从那个时候起我就没让这手表停过
I have never let his watch stop since then.
从那个时候起
And from that moment on,
我带起了一副面具
I created a persona.
我计划着 算好所有的细节
I planned. I worked out every detail.
但是我唯一没有想到会发生的．
But the one thing that I couldn't imagine happening
是你
was you.
就是努力解决这个案件
And I know that the logical conclusion for you
解决这个案子是理所当然的
is to take this case to its resolution.
把我供进去也是应该的
And for you to turn me in.
没错 但是你知道我是怎么看待决心和逻辑的
Yeah. But you know how I feel about resolution and logic.
此外你也知道
And you also know
有些事情也不必要解释
that I think some things are best left unexplained.
又多了一个要被锁起来的秘密
One more secret to lock away.
靠近点
Come in close.
再近点
Closer.
因为现在你知道我们的秘密
Because now you know our secret.
我们无处不在，注视着你
We could be anywhere. Watching you.
我们正在为下一场魔术招兵买马
We're looking for someone to help us with our next trick.
我数到三，睁开你的眼睛
On the count of three, open your eyes
告诉我，你看到了什么
and tell me what you see.
一
One.
二...
Two...
[不要关，还有！彩蛋位置]01：55：55：280
更多翻译、资源请访问
blog.memory-delta.org
快 停车啊
Please, stop, stop, stop.
停车 我要跳车了
All right, stop the van. Stop the van. I'm gonna jump out of the van.
哦 谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
我们在哪儿
Where are we?
太棒了 另一个鬼地方
Great, another shit hole.
好了 感受一下
Okay, feeling it.
我又饿又累又不爽
I'm exhausted, and hungry, and cranky.
四处看一下
Check out this place.
你把我们带到什么鬼地方  这就是个垃圾场？
- Where'd you bring us? - Was there no landfill where we were?
这地方好赞
This place is awesome.
这是我们的新道具吗
Is this our new gear?
最好不是  例如 连衣裤什么的
There'd better not be, like, matching jumpsuits in there.
你知道我不穿紧身衣的
You know I don't wear spandex.
锁住了  - 伙伴们 纸牌
-It's Locked. - Guys, the cards.
什么牌  - 什么意思？ 什么牌
- What card? - What do you mean, "what card"?
好吧
Okay.